Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 21.07.30 18:38:11
片名  48小时 2
等人时要不要喝啤酒什么的？
YOU WANT TO HAVE YOURSELF A BEER OR SOMETHING
WHILE YOU'RE WAITING THERE?
* SILVER HAIR *
* HAS LOST ITS GOLD *
* TREMBLING HANDS AS SHE... *
先生，听见没有？
YOU HEAR ME, MISTER?
* RED CREPE PAPER, MADE... *
给我一整瓶
I'LL TAKE THE BOTTLE.
* HELP A LITTLE OLD LADY *
* BUY A ROSE TODAY... *
你们好，我有什么可以效劳的？
HOWDY, BOYS.
- 啤酒 - 有的
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YOU?
BREWSKIS.
BREWSKIS. YOU GOT IT.
你的啤酒
THERE YOU GO.
* I COULD SMELL THE ROSE *
* IT CAME ALIVE *
* AS I HEARD HER SAY *
* BUY MY ROSES *
* PRETTY ROSES *
* THEY'RE ONLY MADE OF PAPER *
* BUT THEY ONLY COST A DIME **
先付一半，完事后再付另一半
50 NOW, 50 MORE WHEN YOU'RE DONE.
- 几个人 - 就一个
- 又一个警察？ - 不是，他是你的一个朋友
HOW MANY?
JUST ONE.
WHAT IS HE, ANOTHER COP?
NO. MATTER OF FACT, HE'S A FRIEND OF YOURS.
你会喜欢这活儿的
YOU'RE GOING TO LIKE THIS JOB.
他以前是我哥的手下 他先把一包毒品放在我哥那儿
HE WAS IN MY BROTHER'S GANG.
FIRST HE DROPPED A DIME ON HIM...
然后他暗地里向射杀我哥的警察告密
THEN HE RATTED HIM TO THE COP THAT BLEW HIM AWAY.
HEY.
- 我要进去，你要可乐吗？ - 是的，减肥可乐
I'LL TAKE A LOOK. WANT A COKE?
YEAH, DIET.
我们在14号公路附近的西蒙路
WE'RE ON THE SIMMONS ROAD
ABOUT 15 MILES WEST OFF OF ROUTE 14.
我需要有关寻找或追辑摩托车的资料
I NEED WANTS AND WARRANTS ON MOTORCYCLE REGISTRATIONS.
第一个是，加利福尼亚，6D84S9 第二个车牌…
ROGER. I COPY.
FIRST ONE, CALIFORNIA--
6-DAVID-8-4-SAM-NINER.
ROGER. COPY THAT.
SECOND PLATE...
- 汤姆 - 你过的怎么样？见到你真好
TOM.
HOW YOU DOING? NICE TO SEE YOU.
威利・希科克，就是我
WILLIE HICKOK. RIGHT HERE.
柴瑞・甘孜，长官
CHERRY GANZ, OFFICER.
我认识你们吗？
DO I KNOW YOU GUYS?
REPEAT, CODE 6-CHARLES.
- 你给谁打电话呢，朋友？ - 我没给谁打
WHO YOU CALLING, FRIEND?
NO ONE. I WASN'T CALLING NOBODY.
- 不知道为什么我不相信你 - 哦，上帝啊，不要！
SOMEHOW, I DON'T BELIEVE YOU.
OH, GOD! OH, NO!
十万元，先付五万，冰人真是非常慷慨的人
$100,000.
50,000 NOW. ICEMAN'S A GENEROUS GUY.
我不喜欢面值一百的票子，这算什么？
I DON'T LIKE 100s. I TOLD YOU THAT BEFORE.
就这家伙，当他被污染的时候就没了平衡 我们要他死
THIS IS THE GUY.
THE BALANCE IS DUE WHEN HE'S DUSTED, UNDERSTAND?
可以，随便，没问题
WE WANT HIM DEAD.
YEAH, WHATEVER. NO PROBLEM.
警察！不许动！
POLICE! FREEZE!
分开站立，我不希望任何人受伤，慢慢动
YOU, MOVE A STEP APART.
I DON'T WANT ANYBODY GETTING HURT,
SO MOVE SLOW.
可恶！
SHIT!
有警察来了，快他妈的离开这儿！
GET THE HELL OUT OF HERE!
- 你差点把他烤熟 - 我只是向他开枪，没有烤他！
CHRIST, YOU REALLY TOASTED THAT GUY.
I DIDN'T TOAST THE GUY.
I JUST SHOT HIM, FOR CHRIST SAKE.
冷静，我们会找到枪，我们要齐心协力
CALM DOWN. WE'LL FIND THE GUN.
我查过这家伙的储物柜，他在赛车场工作
WE'VE GOT TO DO THIS TOGETHER.
I CHECKED THE GUY'S LOCKER.
他钱包里有50块，太阳镜和一些钥匙
SEEMS OK. WORKS HERE AT THE TRACK.
50 BUCKS IN HIS WALLET, SUNGLASSES, KEYS,
- 我们仍然没有找到他的枪 - 靠！
PROBABLY CAR OR APARTMENT.
WE STILL HAVEN'T FOUND HIS GUN YET.
凯茨击毙了一个赛车场工人 其中一枪打到了油泵
AW, SHIT.
CATES TOOK DOWN ONE OF THE LOCALS.
他把那坏家伙烧焦了 杰克宣称他是合法开枪
A SLUG HIT A GAS PUMP
AND BURNED THE BAD GUY TO A CRISP.
JACK CLAIMS IT WAS A RIGHTEOUS SHOOT.
我讨厌这些内务部的人渣
MAN, I HATE THESE I.A.D. SCUMBAGS.
布雷克・威尔逊，内务部 我经常碰到你，杰克
BLAKE WILSON, INTERNAL AFFAIRS.
给我们一分钟，小伙子们
SEEMS LIKE I'M ALWAYS RUNNING INTO YOU, JACK.
GIVE US A MINUTE, FELLAS.
- 你这次做了什么？ - 我一直在监视
WHAT DID YOU DO NOW, JACK?
- 我几乎捉到… - 几乎？那个冰人，对吗？
I WAS ON A STAKEOUT, GETTING REAL CLOSE--
CLOSE? OH, HO, THE ICEMAN, RIGHT?
我就差一点，我会捉到这些家伙的
YEAH, THE ICEMAN. I'M GOING TO NAIL THESE GUYS.
每一件你解决不了的案子就算在冰人头上
YOU PIN EVERY CASE YOU CAN'T SOLVE ON THE ICEMAN.
海湾区最大的贩子，没有指纹 没有外貌描述
THE BAY AREA'S BIGGEST DRUG DEALER, RIGHT?
你是唯一相信他的存在的警察
EXCEPT WE DON'T HAVE ANY PRINTS OR A DESCRIPTION.
YOU'RE THE ONLY COP WHO BELIEVES THIS GUY EXISTS.
我告诉你一个秘密，不存在什么冰人
I'LL TELL YOU A LITTLE SECRET--
让我们回到冰冷的现实 这儿到底出了什么事？
THERE IS NO ICEMAN.
SO LET'S GET BACK TO THE COLD FACTS HERE,
我看到一桩交易，我行动了，他有枪 他开枪，我还击
BECAUSE THIS IS REAL. WHAT HAPPENED?
I SAW AN EXCHANGE. PROBABLE CAUSE.
HE HAD A PIECE. HE SHOT. I SHOT BACK.
- 你拿到了那坏家伙的枪？ - 它肯定在灰烬里
YOU GOT THE BAD GUY'S GUN?
IT'S GOT TO BE IN THERE WITH THE ASHES AND SHIT.
- 克鲁斯，你找到什么了？ - 一些烧化的金属，油泵上的
CRUISE, WHAT DO YOU GOT?
NOTHING MUCH. JUST SOME BURNT METAL.
- 没有枪？ - 没有，没有枪
MUST BE OFF THE PUMP.
NO GUN?
警察也是人，人有时候会犯错的
NO, NO GUN.
LOOK, A COP IS A GUY,
你可能有点太激进了？
AND A GUY SOMETIMES STEPS ON HIS DICK.
YOU THINK YOU WERE PUSHING TOO HARD
你自己犯过错误没？
TRYING TO MAKE SOMETHING WORK?
WE'RE ON THE SAME SIDE. DID YOU STEP ON--
他有枪，他开枪了，我还击
DAMN IT, HE HAD A PIECE! HE SHOT. I SHOT BACK.
让检查人员好好搜搜 如果有那么一把枪，我要找到它
HAVE THE LAB BOYS GO OVER EVERY INCH.
IF THERE'S A GUN HERE, I WANT IT.
A BULLET. SOMETHING. ANYTHING.
- 回见，杰克 - 好的
SEE YOU AROUND, JACK?
YEAH.
雷吉・哈蒙德
REGGIE HAMMOND.
你肯定是一个非常危险的犯人
YOU MUST BE A REAL DANGEROUS CONVICT.
- 你让我投偏了，警察 - 你看起来很好，雷吉
YOU MADE ME MISS, COP.
YOU LOOK GOOD, REGGIE.
好几年没见了，以前我们是朋友
I AIN'T SEEN YOU IN YEARS.
- 对不起，我以前很忙 - 我也是
THOUGHT YOU WAS MY FRIEND.
I'M SORRY. I'VE BEEN BUSY.
你来这儿做甚？你甚至换了新发型
YEAH, ME, TOO.
YOU MUST BE DESPERATE TO COME DOWN HERE.
时代变了
WHAT'S GOING ON?
- 你瘦了几磅 - 我戒酒了
WELL, TIMES CHANGE.
WELL, YOU LOST A COUPLE OF POUNDS.
你是不是来告诉我我的刑期增加了？
QUIT DRINKING.
DID THE WARDEN PICK YOU
TO TELL ME MY SENTENCE GOT YANKED UP
不，你仍然会明天出狱 我们有点小活儿去做
ANOTHER FIVE YEARS OR SOMETHING?
RELAX. YOU'RE STILL GETTING OUT TOMORROW.
WHEN YOU DO, WE'VE GOT ANOTHER JOB TO DO.
当我离开这儿的时候 把我的钱给我然后离我远点
WE DON'T HAVE SHIT TO DO.
JUST GIVE ME MY MONEY AND WALK AWAY, OK?
我一度当过警察，但不成功
I PLAYED THAT COP SHIT ONCE.
如果你不帮我，我永远也不会把钱还你
I JUST WANT MY MONEY, PLEASE.
IF YOU DON'T HELP ME OUT,
I'M NOT EVER GOING TO GIVE YOU YOUR MONEY BACK.
- 你在跟我开玩笑？ - 不是
YOU'RE FUCKING WITH ME, RIGHT?
我非常信任你才把钱给你的，我相信你
NO.
JACK, I GAVE YOU THAT MONEY IN GOOD FAITH
- 你现在却告诉我不能给我？ - 你现在认清形势了，犯人
BECAUSE YOU SAID I COULD TRUST YOU.
NOW I CAN'T HAVE MY MONEY?
YEAH, NOW YOU GOT THE PICTURE, CONVICT.
- 你搞砸了，哈蒙德 - 我只是自卫
YOU SCREWED UP THIS TIME, HAMMOND.
我为我做的一件案子蹲了两年大牢 我永远也不会否认
IT WAS SELF-DEFENSE.
NOBODY'S BUYING THAT CRAP!
I SERVED TWO YEARS FOR A CRIME I DID.
但我刚刚因为我没做过的劫案蹲了五年牢
I NEVER FUCKING DENIED THAT.
BUT I SPENT FIVE BULLSHIT YEARS HERE.
谋杀犯蹲的时间也比我短
I NEVER ROBBED NO PAYROLL.
你可以住单间了，开门
MURDERERS IN HERE DO LESS TIME THAN ME.
YOU CAN SPEND YOUR REMAINING TIME IN ISOLATION.
OPEN UP.
罗克珊
你不必非得混妓院
* ROXANNE *
* YOU DON'T HAVE TO PUT ON A RED LIGHT *
那些日子已经过去 你不必非得在晚上卖身
* THOSE DAYS ARE OVER *
* YOU DON'T HAVE TO SELL YOUR BODY *
罗克珊
* TO THE NIGHT *
* ROXANNE **
龙舌兰酒，一瓶
TEQUILA.
THE BOTTLE.
- 你们要喝点什么？ - 威士忌，倒杯子里
YOU GUYS WANT ANYTHING?
WHISKEY. PUT IT IN A GLASS.
普莱斯先生，这人很悲伤
MR. PRICE, THE MAN IS DISTRESSED.
沙漠那烂摊子 让他怀疑你的人能不能干这活儿
THAT MESS YOU MADE IN THE DESERT HAS HIM WONDERING
不用担心
IF YOU'LL BE AROUND TO FINISH THE JOB.
NOT TO WORRY.
真正的专业？我看不像
REAL PROS, HUH?
干活的时候你不应该惹事生非
NOT FROM WHERE I'M SITTING.
PROS DON'T MAKE MESSES LIKE YOU DID.
DON'T GET THE HEAT JACKED UP
如果你想当亡命徒，那就没有规矩
WHEN YOU'RE DOING A JOB.
YOU WANT TO BE AN OUTLAW BUT PLAY BY RULES.
- 这是你的哲学？ - 我们是仅存的真正美国人
THERE AIN'T NO RULES.
YOU GIVING ME YOUR PHILOSOPHY?
THAT'S RIGHT, BRO. WE'RE THE ONLY REAL AMERICANS LEFT.
我们信仰自由 我们的生活方式一如既往
WE BELIEVE IN FREEDOM.
在有大城市，律师 有你名字的电脑之前，自由！
WE LIVE THE WAY FOLKS USED TO,
BACK BEFORE THERE WERE BIG CITIES AND LAWYERS
AND COMPUTERS WITH YOUR NAMES IN THEM.
那时你们只是一群他妈的奴隶
FREE. THE REST OF YOU
ARE JUST A BUNCH OF FUCKING SLAVES.
真的很有趣，普莱斯先生 或许你该参加竞选
YEAH? THAT SOUNDS REAL INTERESTING, MR. PRICE.
我觉得应该告诉你要警惕
MAYBE YOU SHOULD RUN FOR OFFICE.
ALL I'M SUPPOSED TO TELL YOU IS TAKE PRECAUTIONS.
你的助手在赛车场被烧焦了
YOUR BACKUP GOT BARBECUED AT A RACE TRACK.
- 这些你知道怎么用吗？ - 没问题，朋友
YOU KNOW WHAT TO DO WITH THAT STUFF.
- 我当过海军 - 不出所料
NO PROBLEM HERE, FRIEND.
I USED TO BE A MARINE.
有麻烦就来找我，你知道号码
I GUESS THAT FIGURES.
YOU GUYS HAVE ANY TROUBLE, YOU COME TO ME.
YOU KNOW THE NUMBER.
嘿，过来
HEY. HEY, COME HERE.
你找错姑娘了，我不做那事的
I THINK YOU GOT THE WRONG GIRL. I DON'T DO THAT.
来吧，我的朋友和我刚来到这镇子
COME ON. MY FRIEND AND I JUST CAME INTO TOWN.
我们再找这儿的一个妓女 名字叫安琪的
WE'RE LOOKING FOR A WHORE WORKING HERE.
WHAT'S HER NAME?
她正在北湾跳舞
NAME'S ANGEL.
ANGEL DON'T WORK HERE ANYMORE.
- 你呢？ - 我不喜欢这样，放开！
SHE'S IN NORTH BEACH.
WELL, YOU'RE HERE. HOW ABOUT YOU?
- 我要报警了 - 去吧，去报吧
I'M GETTING TIRED OF THIS--LET GO!
OTHERWISE, I'LL CALL THE COPS.
GO AHEAD, SWEET CHEEKS.
我们上路吧，伙计们，来啊，柴瑞
CALL 'EM.
HEY, LET'S HIT THE ROAD, BOYS. COME ON.
COME ON, CHERRY.
在亨特角赛车场发生的枪击事件
"IN THE MATTER OF THE OFFICER-INVOLVED SHOOTING
嫌犯亚瑟・布洛克，旧金山居民
"AT HUNTER'S POINT RACEWAY OF THE SUSPECT ARTHUR BROCK,
审查局已经仔细研究过证据
"A RESIDENT OF SAN FRANCISCO,
"THE REVIEW BOARD HAS CAREFULLY EXAMINED
认定涉案警察，杰克・凯茨探员
"THE PHYSICAL EVIDENCE AND THE WITNESSES' TESTIMONY,
"AND HAS DETERMINED THAT THE OFFICER IN QUESTION,
没有足够理由指证被害人
"INSPECTOR JACK CATES,
鉴于内务部的调查仍在进行
"HAD INSUFFICIENT PROBABLE CAUSE.
"BASED ON A REVIEW OF THE OFFICER'S CASE HISTORY
"AND AN ONGOING INVESTIGATION
审查局的判决是当时开枪是错误行为
"BY THE INTERNAL AFFAIRS DIVISION,
"THIS REVIEW BOARD CANNOT HELP BUT RULE
THAT THE SHOOTING WAS A WRONGFUL ACTION."
我从没想到他们会真的为难你
你将会收到过失杀人指控 我希望会找到那枪
I NEVER THOUGHT THEY'D LAND ON YOU SO HARD.
I'LL HAVE TO RECOMMEND
THAT YOU BE PROSECUTED FOR MANSLAUGHTER.
- 对不起，杰克，我只是在执行公务 - 好吧！
I WISH THEY'D FOUND THAT GUN.
WELL, I'M SORRY, JACK.
I'M JUST DOING MY JOB.
RIGHT.
你的个人简介说你有经常过火的记录
WILSON'S GOT A PERSONALITY PROFILE OF AN OBSESSED COP
WHOSE RECORD SHOWS HIS HISTORY OF OVERSTEPPING THE LINE.
地方法官极有可能选择控告你三级谋杀
IT'S LIKELY THE D.A. WILL CHOOSE TO PROSECUTE YOU
- 换句话说，你麻烦大了 - 除非我找到冰人
ON THIRD DEGREE.
IN OTHER WORDS, YOU'RE SCREWED.
放弃吧，杰克，那就是导致你如此的原因
UNLESS I FIND THE ICEMAN.
GIVE IT UP. THAT'S WHAT GOT YOU INTO THIS.
我的天啊，你听起来就像威尔逊
我们在讨论事实，你摸不清方向 部门也摸不清方向
JESUS CHRIST, YOU SOUND LIKE WILSON.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE FACTS HERE.
这是过失杀人，保护你自己
YOU GOT NO LEADS. THE DEPARTMENT'S GOT NO LEADS.
THIS IS MANSLAUGHTER.
PROTECT YOURSELF.
[CELL DOOR OPENS]
哈蒙德，我们走，这是你的大日子
HAMMOND, LET'S GO.
- 让我出去就好 - 是的，是的，来吧
BIG DAY FOR YOU TODAY.
JUST GET ME OUT OF HERE.
YEAH, YEAH. COME ON.
雷吉
- 过来 - 对不起
REGGIE.
COME HERE.
你会遵守你的诺言，是吧？
EXCUSE ME A MINUTE.
YOU WILL KEEP YOUR PROMISE, RIGHT?
别担心，所有事都办妥
EVERYTHING IS-- DON'T WORRY, EVERYTHING IS COOL.
来这儿的那白人警察是找麻烦的吗？
IT'S NO PROBLEM.
THAT WHITE COP THAT VISITED YOU YESTERDAY--
不！我答应过你，所有事都办妥
HE AIN'T NO PROBLEM, IS HE?
NO, HE AIN'T GOING TO FUCK THINGS UP, I PROMISE YOU.
但时间可能比我说的要长点
EVERYTHING IS COOL,
BUT...IT MIGHT TAKE A LITTLE LONGER THAN I SAID.
别蒙我了，把钱拿来以保守诺言
DON'T BULLSHIT ME, MAN.
YOU GET THAT MONEY, AND YOU KEEP YOUR WORD.
我让你在这老鼠洞存活了五年
I KEPT YOU ALIVE IN THIS FUNKY RATHOLE FOR FIVE YEARS,
我能让你离开这儿，我也能弄死你
SO DON'T ACT LIKE EVERYTHING IS EVERYTHING.
I CAN GET YOU OUT THERE.
I CAN PULL YOUR FUCKING HEART OUT.
- 这都为了什么？ - 赌球的旧账
WHAT WAS ALL THAT GOING ON BACK THERE?
那都是废话，哈蒙德・雷吉
TALKING ABOUT A FOOTBALL BET.
THAT'S A CROCK.
HAMMOND, REGGIE A.
100美元和一趟去旧金山的免费巴士
HERE'S $100 IN CASH AND A FREE BUS RIDE TO SAN FRANCISCO,
全都是加州免费提供的
- 就这些？ - 是啊
COMPLIMENTS OF THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA.
谢谢你没有跟我说其它废话
THAT'S IT?
THAT'S IT.
THANK YOU FOR SPARING ME THE OTHER CRAP.
不要这样乱扔我东西
MAN, DON'T SLAM MY SHIT DOWN LIKE THAT.
我的詹姆斯・布朗的带子呢？ 这东西没了
HEY, WHERE'S MY JAMES BROWN TAPE?
没人能让我和詹姆斯待在监狱里
THE SHIT AIN'T IN--OH.
EVERYBODY TRYING TO KEEP ME AND JAMES IN PRISON.
- 我们还没说完呢 - 把他妈的钱给我
WE DIDN'T GET TO FINISH OUR CONVERSATION.
不帮我就拿不到钱
STAY AWAY TILL YOU GET MY MONEY, OK?
I SAID YOU AIN'T GETTING YOUR MONEY
我相信你才把车和钱给你，你却骗我
UNLESS YOU HELP ME.
LOOK, I TRUSTED YOU, AND YOU FUCKED ME.
我四年前抓过一个叫冰人的毒贩
WHAT'S GOING ON, MAN?
I'VE BEEN CHASING A DRUG DEALER CALLED THE ICEMAN.
上周我发现他要弄死你
LAST WEEK I FIND OUT ICEMAN WANTS YOU DEAD.
从要杀你的人那儿我得到的线索 你认识他吗？
HERE, TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
I FOUND THIS ON A GUY PAYING SOMEONE TO KILL YOU.
四年来，你是我最好的线人
RECOGNIZE THIS GUY? HUH?
IN FOUR YEARS, YOU'RE THE BEST LEAD I EVER HAD.
是吗？不还钱我不会帮你的
HELPING YOU WHILE YOU GOT MY MONEY
你让我在监狱受了五年苦 然后要我帮你？
IS SOMETHING I WON'T DO.
I ROT IN PRISON, AND YOU WANT HELP. THAT'S BULLSHIT.
- 这太蠢了，哥们！ - 这次大不一样的
THAT'S WORSE THAN BULLSHIT. THAT'S DUMB!
REGGIE, THIS TIME I PROMISE IT'S GOING TO BE DIFFERENT.
我会失去我的警徽，他们要把我送进大牢
NOW LOOK, I'M GOING TO LOSE MY BADGE.
你惹上官司了？太好了
THEY'RE GOING TO PUT ME IN JAIL.
YOU'RE IN TROUBLE WITH THE LAW THIS TIME? GOOD.
这感觉就跟我拿不到钱一样吧 我感觉好受多了
AS BAD AS I FEEL ABOUT MY MONEY,
等一下，我不是在乞求！
THAT SHIT ALMOST MAKES ME FEEL BETTER.
你想咋的，开枪打我？ 我是你曾有过的最好的线人
WAIT A MINUTE. I DON'T BEG!
YOU GOING TO WHIP MY ASS?
SHOOT ME IN FRONT OF THE PRISON?
以后的五六年我会来看你的
THAT'S NO WAY TO TREAT YOUR BEST LEAD.
I'LL COME VISIT YOU IN FIVE OR SIX YEARS.
- 出发 - 我们有日程表
LET'S GET OUT OF HERE.
- 我不再用美国时间了 - 写信吧
HEY, WE GOT A SCHEDULE.
FUCK THAT. I'M NOT ON THE STATE'S TIME NO MORE.
WRITE A LETTER.
EVERYBODY AROUND THIS MOTHERFUCKER'S CRAZY.
蓝色凯迪拉克车那他妈的大个子就是杀我哥那人
BIG FUCKER IN THE BLUE CADDY.
太棒了，哥们，我把他俩都找到了
THAT'S THE PIG WHO WASTED MY BROTHER.
THIS IS GREAT, MAN. I GET THEM BOTH.
[HORN HONKS]
* LAST NIGHT *
* I HAD A LITTLE TALK WITH MYSELF *
* JUST ME AND ME *
* MAN TO MAN *
* I SAID, SELF, I THINK IT'S TIME *
* I LAID IT ON THE LINE *
* AND I TRIED MY BEST *
* TO MAKE ME UNDERSTAND *
* ALL THEM YEARS *
* AND THEM TEARS *
* OVER A LOVE THAT'S GROWN COLD *
* IT'S WASTIN' TIME *
* YOURS AND MINE... **
你不知道你对我做了什么
* YOU DON'T KNOW *
* WHAT YOU DO TO ME *
让我痛苦
* GET ME DOWN *
* HEY! IN MISERY *
哦，耶，先生！好吧！哦，耶，先生！
YEAH!
* AH, YES, SIR *
嘿…开枪打我！好吧
* WELL *
* AH, YES, SIR *
HEY!
噢…哼！哼！哼！噢…
* HIT ME, ALL RIGHT *
WAAOW!
真想亲自己一口！美妙上帝！好！
HUH, HUH, HUH, WAAOW!
* WANNA KISS MYSELF-- GOOD GOD *
我能感受到！嘿…
* WELL *
* AND I GOT TO FEEL IT, HEY *
好！哦！
* WELL *
宝贝，宝贝，宝贝！宝贝，宝贝，宝贝！
OW!
* BABY, BABY, BABY *
宝贝，宝贝，宝贝！宝贝，宝贝，喔…
* BABY, BABY, WAAOW *
想要继续…继续好走！哦，美妙上帝！
* WANT TO GET ON THE GOOD FOOT *
嘿！噢…只是有时我…当我走进教堂…
GOOD GOD! HEY! WAAOW!
* SEPTEMBER, WHEN THE GOOD CHECKS COME *
耶…
YEAH!
宝贝，宝贝，宝贝！宝贝，宝贝，宝贝！宝贝…
* BABY, BABY, BABY *
* BABY, BABY, BABY, BABY *
趴下！
GET DOWN!
我在50号高速公路上往西行驶
I'M WESTBOUND ON HIGHWAY 50--
需要增援，马上，我需要增援！
GET SOME HELP OUT HERE NOW!
I NEED SOME HELP NOW!
SHIT!
[HORN HONKS]
上
LET'S GO.
走
[SIREN]
COME ON!
快走！
你左侧锁骨裂了
表皮有点外伤
YOU GOT A HAIRLINE FRACTURE OF YOUR LEFT CLAVICLE.
- 你经常穿防弹衣吗？ - 只有当我看见朋友的时候
BLUNT TRAUMA BROKE THE SKIN.
RIGHT.
DO YOU ALWAYS WEAR A BULLETPROOF VEST?
我要你每小时换一次胸口的绷带
ONLY WHEN I SEE MY FRIENDS.
I WANT YOU TO CHANGE THE BANDAGE ON YOUR CHEST
我必须固定这胳膊，套上挂带
EVERY HOUR AND A HALF.
ALL RIGHT.
I HAVE TO IMMOBILIZE THIS ARM, SO WEAR THIS SLING.
- 你要去哪儿？ - 我要去执行公务
ALL RIGHT. THANKS, DOC.
WHERE ARE YOU GOING?
我在忙活自己的，那些飞车党就开始射击
YOUR LAB REPORTS HAVEN'T ARRIVED.
I GOT POLICE BUSINESS.
I WAS MINDING MY OWN BUSINESS,
- 看X光片没事 - 但我的头仍然在疼
AND THOSE BIKERS STARTED SHOOTING AT THE BUS.
你坐的那巴士翻车
YOUR X-RAYS ARE FINE.
HOW COME MY HEAD STILL HURTS?
你可能有点轻微脑震荡，但你很走运
A BUS ROLLED OVER ON YOU.
YOU MIGHT HAVE A SLIGHT CONCUSSION
- 我们得留你过夜 - 你们不能让我过夜
OR A SUBDURAL HEMATOMA.
WE'RE HOLDING YOU OVERNIGHT.
我要回家，我不想出来第一天就在医院过
YOU'RE NOT HOLDING ME.
ME AND MY SUBDURAL HEMATOMA ARE GOING HOME.
你要在这儿回答问题 你以前见没见过那些飞车党？
I'M NOT STAYING IN NO HOSPITAL.
YOU'LL BE HERE TILL YOU ANSWER OUR QUESTIONS.
我看你们这些乡巴佬都一个样
YOU NEVER SAW THOSE BIKERS BEFORE?
- 看着他，亚特 - 棒极了，亚特，这该死的乡巴佬
ALL YOU REDNECKS LOOK THE SAME.
KEEP ON HIM. I'LL BE BACK.
GREAT. I'M SPENDING MY FIRST DAY OUT WITH A REDNECK.
我正拿着这家伙的早餐走出厨房
I WAS CARRYING THIS GUY'S BREAKFAST.
他看起来有点滑稽，不只是饿 而且为什么事在发疯
I WAS WORRIED I'D BE LATE BECAUSE HE LOOKED FUNNY.
NOT JUST HUNGRY--LIKE HE'S MAD AT SOMETHING.
接下来便开枪然后窗玻璃都碎了…
THE NEXT THING I KNOW, THERE'S THESE BIG GUNSHOTS,
- 哈蒙德，我什么时候能看他？ - 我要留他过夜
AND THE WINDOW'S BREAKING, AND...
WHEN CAN I SEE REGGIE HAMMOND?
I'D HELP IF I COULD.
真是个幸运的人，我想跟他去赌马
THEY'RE KEEPING HIM OVERNIGHT FOR OBSERVATION.
THAT'S ONE LUCKY GUY.
你知道他为什么坐牢吗？这混蛋侵犯儿童
I'D LIKE TO FOLLOW HIM AROUND THE RACE TRACK.
YOU KNOW WHAT HE WAS IN THE JOINT FOR?
NO.
他涉嫌儿童色情刊物 我今晚必须带他到旧金山
HE'S A CHILD MOLESTER. HE'S INVOLVED IN KIDDIE PORN.
I GOT TO GET HIM BACK TO SAN FRANCISCO TONIGHT
他要指证主谋，如果今晚我不带他去 主谋便逍遥法外了
SO HE CAN IDENTIFY THE ORGANIZATION'S KINGPIN.
IF I DON'T GET HIM BACK TONIGHT,
THE GOD DAMN KINGPIN WALKS.
你想开凯迪拉克去吗？
HEY, REGGIE.
我今天很不顺，除了你我什么也不想要
WANT TO RIDE IN A CADILLAC?
I'VE BEEN HAVING A FUCKED-UP DAY.
我只是想帮你
THE LAST THING I WANTED TO SEE WAS YOU.
I'M JUST TRYING TO HELP YOU.
你能赶上巴士，你上次坐巴士很走运
YOU COULD ALWAYS CATCH A BUS.
帮我个忙，离我远点
YOU WERE LUCKY WITH THE LAST ONE.
DO ME A FAVOR AND DISAPPEAR.
对不起，雷吉，他们放你是让我看着你
STAY AWAY FROM ME.
I'M SORRY, REG.
THEY RELEASED YOU IN MY CUSTODY.
- 你以前见过那些飞车党吗？ - 我的钱在哪儿？
LET'S GET DOWN TO BUSINESS.
YOU EVER SEEN THOSE BIKERS BEFORE?
你告诉我冰人为什么想杀你 你就可以拿到钱
MY MEMORY'S BETTER WHEN I GOT MONEY.
YOU KNOW THE RULES.
- 问那个有我照片的家伙 - 他说不了了，我杀了他
SOON AS YOU TELL ME
WHY THE ICEMAN WANTS YOU DEAD,
I'LL GIVE YOU YOUR MONEY.
ASK THE GUY WHO HAD MY PICTURE.
- 他们给你多少钱？ - 他先开枪打我的
HE'S NOT TALKING. I KILLED HIM.
DO THEY PAY YOU BY THE POUND NOW?
- 只是我们找不到他的枪 - 你希望得到同情吗？
HE SHOT AT ME FIRST,
ONLY WE CAN'T FIND HIS GUN.
我应该在佛罗里达经营我叔叔的二手车生意
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR SYMPATHY,
YOU'VE COME TO THE WRONG PERSON.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE OFF TO FLORIDA
相反的是我穷困潦倒，被枪打 坐的巴士翻滚了二十次
TO BE IN MY UNCLE'S USED CAR BUSINESS.
INSTEAD I'M WITH YOU, I'M BROKE, I'VE BEEN SHOT AT,
MY BUS FLIPPED 20 TIMES,
我弄坏了随身听，我被大卡车撞 所以让我静静
I HAD GLASS IN MY HAIR AND SUIT,
BROKE MY WALKMAN AND LOST MY JAMES BROWN TAPE.
生活真是艰难，我碰到了你的朋友 他们对我胸口开了六枪
PLUS I'VE BEEN HIT BY A TRUCK,
SO LEAVE ME ALONE.
LIFE'S TOUGH.
I RAN INTO YOUR FRIENDS, TOO.
- 你看上去比死人强点 - 我正戴着这玩意
THEY SHOT ME IN THE CHEST SIX TIMES.
YOU DON'T LOOK BAD FOR A DEAD PERSON.
- 为什么？ - 我知道我会遇见你的
I WOULD BE IF IT WASN'T FOR THIS.
WHY DO YOU WEAR THIS?
我不想被射向你的流弹所杀
I KNEW I WAS GOING TO SEE YOU.
I WOULDN'T WANT TO GET KILLED
BY A BULLET MEANT FOR YOU.
你认为我应该穿一件？
THAT'D BE A HELL OF A WAY TO GO.
大约750美元一件 你出狱时没给你这么多钱
THAT'S VERY SENSITIVE, JACK.
SHOULD I GET ONE OF THESE?
YOU CAN GET THEM AT ANY SPORTING GOODS.
THEY RUN ABOUT $750.
- 我希望我的保时捷在你那儿 - 我说了我保管的很好
A LITTLE MORE THAN THEY GAVE YOU.
I HOPE YOU GOT MY PORSCHE.
IT'S SAFE IN THE CITY.
那没什么意义，你说我们有交易 然后你耍了我
I TOOK REAL GOOD CARE OF IT.
HEY, MAN, YOU SAID WE HAD A DEAL.
你耍了你自己，你偷走了监狱的薪水
YOU FUCKED ME.
I FUCKED YOU?
YOU FUCKED YOURSELF.
- 我查过了 - 我是冤枉的
YOU STOLE THE PAYROLL AT THE PRISON.
THEY FOUND THE MONEY IN YOUR CELL.
对，有犯人让警卫把钱放到你监舍里的
MOTHERFUCKER, I GOT FRAMED.
SOME CONVICT GOT A GUARD TO OPEN THE CELL,
- 你当然是被冤枉的 - 那你呢？
PUT THE MONEY UNDER THE PILLOW LIKE THE TOOTH FAIRY.
YOU GOT FRAMED? THAT'S WHAT EVERY CONVICT SAYS.
他们在赛车场没找到那人的枪
THEY NEVER FOUND THAT GUY'S GUN AT THE RACE TRACK.
- 我是警察，你是罪犯 - 所以我说的每句话都是他妈的谎话？
THAT'S DIFFERENT.
WHAT'S DIFFERENT ABOUT THAT?
I'M A COP. YOU'RE A CROOK.
JUST BECAUSE I'M A CONVICT, I'M A LIAR?
带我去我的车那儿吧，我受够你了
THAT'S RIGHT.
SO JUST SCREW REGGIE HAMMOND!
怎么了，你胳膊疼吗？疼的厉害吗？好
JUST TAKE ME TO MY CAR.
I'M THROUGH WITH YOU.
YOUR ARM HURT?
YEAH. THANKS TO YOUR FRIENDS.
我们有麻烦了，滑头
HURT BAD?
YEAH.
GOOD.
YOU HEAR THE NEWS?
这些乡下人不是我雇的 所以不要向我投诉
WE GOT A PROBLEM HERE, SLICK.
HEY, MAN, BACK UP.
I DIDN'T HIRE THESE HILLBILLIES,
对，B计划，我们找到了一位退伍海军
SO DON'T COMPLAIN TO ME.
YES. PLAN B.
唯一的问题是，他也是个乡下人
WE GOT AN EX-MARINE ON THE CASE.
ONLY PROBLEM IS, HE'S A HILLBILLY, TOO.
对，等会儿
YEAH.
RIGHT.
LATER.
- 你花了多少钱？ - 大概两万五
HOW MUCH OF MY MONEY DID YOU SPEND?
- 你说我可以买一辆新车 - 在哪儿呢？
ABOUT 25 GRAND.
YOU SAID I COULD BUY A NEW CAR.
- 这就是一辆新车 - 这辆老的就像一堆屎
WELL, WHERE IS IT?
THIS HERE'S THE NEW CAR.
THIS LOOKS LIKE THE SAME SHITTY SKY-BLUE CADILLAC YOU HAD BEFORE.
我买了同一型号，年份，颜色的 我就喜欢这样的
I BOUGHT THE SAME MODEL, YEAR, COLOR, EVERYTHING THE SAME.
你的车和衣服都没变
I GET ATTACHED TO THINGS, REGGIE.
- 你女朋友也没变？ - 艾琳？
YOU GOT THE SAME CAR?
YEAH.
SAME CLOTHES.
- 我不想说这个 - 都闷在自己心里吧
YOU GOT THE SAME GIRL, TOO?
ELAINE?
I DON'T WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS SHIT.
五年前她和我在市政厅结婚
KEEP IT ALL BALLED UP.
SHE MARRIED ME ABOUT FIVE YEARS AGO.
她认为她能让我变成居家男人
DROVE ME TO CITY HALL FOR A QUICK CEREMONY.
SHE FIGURED SHE'D SETTLE ME DOWN.
我们分手之前一直住这儿
THIS IS WHERE WE LIVED TILL WE SPLIT UP.
我想卖了它，首付用了你的一万二
SHE MOVED UP TO MILL VALLEY.
I'VE BEEN TRYING TO SELL IT.
你怎么能把我的车停在外面？ 有人偷了怎么办？
12 GRAND OF YOURS WENT FOR THE DOWN PAYMENT.
HOW COULD YOU LEAVE MY CAR OUTSIDE ALL THESE YEARS?
WHY DIDN'T YOU PUT IT IN THE GARAGE?
我安了防盗系统，只要按这蓝色按钮
WHAT IF SOMEBODY STOLE IT?
I HAD AN ALARM PUT IN IT.
你不会欣赏什么是有型有款
JUST PUSH THAT BLUE BUTTON THERE.
YOU HAVE NO APPRECIATION FOR WHAT'S HYPE.
你知道因为这车搞到多少女人？
THAT CAR IS FLY.
YOU KNOW HOW MUCH PUSSY I GOT BECAUSE OF THAT CAR?
他们炸毁了我的车！
- 他们炸毁了我的车！ - 真可惜
THEY BLEW UP MY CAR!
- 你只会说这个？ - 你今天运气不好
THAT'S A DAMN SHAME.
THEY BLEW UP MY CAR,
AND ALL YOU GOT TO SAY IS IT'S A DAMN SHAME?
我对你受够了，我要给我老朋友打电话
NO CAR. NO MONEY. YOU'RE HAVING A BAD DAY.
THAT'S IT. I'M THROUGH WITH YOU.
我要借点钱，我要离开！
I'M CALLING SOME OF MY HOMIES.
I'M GETTING A LOAN.
I'M STEPPING THE FUCK OFF.
帅哥，过的咋样？我是雷吉・哈蒙德
BUSTER! HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
对，我的兄弟！我出来了，我重返街头
HOW YOU DOING? REGGIE HAMMOND.
YES, MY BROTHER!
是，酷，听着…
I'M OUT, MY MAN. ON THE STREET AGAIN.
是的，我知道，我正打算这样做呢 这就是我为什么打电话，我想借点钱
YEAH. YEAH. JUST COOL IT, BROTHER.
NO, NO, NO. LISTEN.
I'M GOING TO DO THAT.
THAT'S WHAT I'M CALLING ABOUT.
我知道还欠你一些，但我刚出狱啊
I NEED A LOAN.
I KNOW I OWE YOU SOME SHIT,
BUT I JUST GOT OUT OF JAIL.
听着…我没有抵押品，我刚出狱啊
JUST LISTEN.
I DON'T HAVE NO COLLATERAL.
我还需要抵押品吗？ 我是雷吉・哈蒙德啊，嘿…
I JUST GOT OUT OF JAIL.
WHAT THE FUCK I NEED COLLATERAL FOR?
嘿，帅哥？帅哥…
HEY! HEY!
HEY, BUSTER?
BUSTER?
- 我听说你的房子被炸了 - 不是我的房子，是车
JACK, WHAT THE HELL'S GOING ON?
- 你的车被炸了？ - 不是，某人停在前面的
WE GOT REPORTS YOU WERE SHOT
AND YOUR HOUSE BLEW UP.
NO, A CAR.
YOUR CAR BLEW UP?
IT WASN'T MY CAR.
- 有那些飞车党的资料吗？ - 没有，我再找找
IT WAS SOME OTHER GUY'S CAR.
ANYTHING COME IN ON THOSE BIKERS?
你必须得去看看威尔逊，如果你不去 他就会派人来找你
NOT YET. I'LL CHECK AGAIN.
DO ME A FAVOR AND GO SEE WILSON.
HE SAID IF YOU DON'T SEE HIM,
HE'LL SEND SOMEBODY OUT TO GET YOU.
SHIT.
杰克，你还好吧？
HEY, JACK. YOU OK?
你给了他一张票？好的，他讨厌警察
YOU GIVING THAT GUY A TICKET?
- 是吗？ - 是的，他载我过来的
GOOD. HE HATES COPS.
HE DOES, HUH?
他说警察都是藏在警徽后面的娘们
I RODE HERE WITH HIM.
HE SAID COPS AIN'T SHIT.
他说他才不管是不是禁停区
YOU WAS JUST PUSSIES HIDING BEHIND YOUR BADGES.
HE SAID HE'LL PARK THIS CAR--
他说那样某个警察就要倒霉了
HE DON'T CARE IF IT'S A NO-PARKING ZONE.
HE SAID TELL THE COP TO KISS HIS ASS.
你的朋友不太聪明
SO KISS HIS ASS.
YOUR FRIEND'S NOT TOO SMART.
他是一个大块头的蠢警察，名叫杰克・凯茨
YEAH. I KNOW.
HE'S A BIG DUMB-ASS COP NAMED JACK CATES.
告诉凯茨不要停在这儿
SHIT. TELL CATES TO STOP PARKING
IN FRONT OF THE STATION.
你好，杰克
摩托车赛道，然后是餐厅 现在你家有个炸弹
HELLO, JACK.
FIRST THE MOTORCYCLE TRACK, THEN THE DINER.
冰人很忙
NOW WE FOUND A BOMB AT YOUR HOUSE?
我不是来这儿跟你吵的，我是来帮你的
AND THE ICEMAN'S RESPONSIBLE, RIGHT?
I'M NOT GOING TO ARGUE WITH YOU.
但是，作为内务部主管，我必须告诉你
I'M HERE TO SUPPORT YOU.
HOWEVER, AS SUPERVISOR OF INTERNAL AFFAIRS,
IT'S MY JOB TO TELL YOU
在明天聆讯之前你是暂时停职的
YOU'RE STILL ON SUSPENSION,
AT LEAST UNTIL THE COURT HEARING TOMORROW.
所以把枪，警徽，还有工作证给我
SO WHY DON'T YOU GIVE ME THAT GUN
是啊，好吧
AND YOUR BADGE AND POLICE I.D.?
我敢打赌你认为我喜欢这样
YEAH. RIGHT.
I'LL BET YOU THINK I ENJOY THIS, DON'T YOU?
杰克，帮我个忙，回家睡觉
JACK, DO ME A FAVOR.
GO HOME AND GET SOME SLEEP.
我得走了，还有报告要弄
I GOT TO CHECK OUT A FEW THINGS,
MAKE OUT SOME REPORTS.
我不介意有人调查警察 我们不能凌驾于法律之上
I DON'T MIND PEOPLE CHECKING UP ON COPS.
但让警察自己调查自己会影响士气 对警察没什么好处
I DON'T THINK WE'RE ABOVE THE LAW.
BUT MAKING COPS DO IT,
IT'S BAD FOR MORALE.
应该让平民做这个 你真是一个胆小鬼，威尔逊
IT'S BAD FOR COPS.
CIVILIANS OUGHT TO DO IT.
也许不是你的错，也许你只是职责所在
YOU'RE A REAL CHICKENSHIT, WILSON.
BUT MAYBE IT'S NOT YOUR FAULT.
MAYBE IT'S YOUR JOB.
好吧
ALL RIGHT.
马文，过的好吗？雷吉・哈蒙德…哈蒙德
YO, MARVIN!
HEY, WHAT'S UP, MAN?
你好吗？我刚出来，是的兄弟
REGGIE HAMMOND.
HA-HAMMOND.
YEAH. YEAH. YEAH. HOW YOU DOING, MAN?
什么？你是重生的基督信徒？拉倒吧
I JUST GOT OUT.
YEAH, LISTEN.
WHAT?
YOU A BORN AGAIN CHRISTIAN?
我怎么看你也不像一个重生的基督信徒
GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE.
I JUST CAN'T PICTURE YOU BEING--
我曾目睹你殴打那个妓女
I WAS THERE WHEN YOU BEAT THE BITCH UP.
不，每个人都可以找到耶稣，我爱耶稣
NO. DON'T GET ME WRONG.
I KNOW YOU CAN FIND JESUS.
我爱耶稣，我爱耶稣，喂？喂…
EVERYBODY CAN FIND JESUS.
I LOVE JESUS. I LOVE JESUS.
I LOVE--HELLO?
威利・百吉斯，雷吉・哈蒙德 喂…？该死的黑鬼！
HELLO? HELLO? MARVIN?
HEY, WILLIE BIGGS!
REGGIE HAMMOND.
HELLO? HELLO?
BLACK MOTHERFUCKER.
过去四天里有飞车党涉及13宗案件
HERE YOU GO, JACK.
13 COMPLAINTS INVOLVING BIKERS IN THE LAST FOUR DAYS.
- 两宗交通事故，一宗北湾闹事 - 用电脑查这些人
TWO TRAFFICS AND A D AND D IN NORTH BEACH.
我会让克鲁斯去做的，我看他不像飞车党
RUN THEM THROUGH THE NCIC.
I'LL HAVE CRUISE DO IT.
DON'T LOOK MUCH LIKE A BIKER TO ME.
跟你谈话很愉快
NICE TALKING TO YOU.
- 你还在这儿？ - 我不喜欢待在这儿
YOU STILL HERE?
I DIDN'T THINK YOU'D STICK AROUND.
我应该自由自在的，过自己的生活 而不是跟你们这帮蠢材纠缠不清
I'M NOT HAPPY ABOUT BEING HERE.
I'M SUPPOSED TO BE A FREE MAN WITH MONEY IN MY POCKET.
- 欢迎回来 - 离我远点，我不是犯人
I DON'T WANT TO BE TIED TO YOUR WHITE ASS AGAIN.
WELCOME BACK, REG.
我自由了，你就快去我昨天待的地方了 你管不了事了
GET THE FUCK OFF ME.
I AIN'T NO CONVICT. I'M A FREE MAN.
YOU'RE ALMOST WHERE I WAS YESTERDAY.
我不是给你干活，我也不喜欢你
YOU AIN'T RUNNING JACK SHIT.
I AIN'T WORKING FOR YOU,
别说废话了，给我些有用的东西
I DON'T LIKE YOU, AND I DON'T TRUST YOU.
NOW JUST CUT THE BULLSHIT.
冰人买了你的房子
GIVE ME SOMETHING I CAN USE, REGGIE.
THE ICEMAN?
- 别说废话了！ - 你还是没搞清楚
THE ICEMAN BOUGHT YOUR HOUSE.
NOW GOD DAMN IT,
I SAID CUT THE BULLSHIT.
甘孜和我拿了冰人50万美元 他现在还在生气呢
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DIDN'T PUT THIS TOGETHER YET.
ME AND GANZ ROBBED SOMEBODY
FOR $500,000 A COUPLE YEARS BACK.
THAT WAS THE ICEMAN.
看见有些人如何被金钱影响真是让人惊奇
HE'S STILL PISSED OFF.
AMAZING HOW MONEY AFFECTS SOME PEOPLE.
对，你一直在找的人…
I SEE YOUR WHEELS TURNING.
THE MAN YOU'VE BEEN LOOKING FOR
给你买了他妈的车和付了房款的首付
BOUGHT YOUR FUCKED-UP CAR
AND PUT A DOWN PAYMENT ON YOUR HOUSE.
那让你成为了全体执法人员里 最蠢的一个混蛋
YOU'RE RIDING IN HIS CAR LOOKING FOR HIM,
WHICH MAKES YOU THE DUMBEST MOTHERFUCKER IN LAW ENFORCEMENT.
我来开车，你搞砸了 与你不同，我活的很有意义
GET IN THE CAR. I'M DRIVING.
YOU GOT A FUCKED-UP ARM.
I'M NOT GETTING IN ANOTHER WRECK.
I, UNLIKE YOU, HAVE A LOT TO LIVE FOR.
我总想有个司机
I ALWAYS WANTED A CHAUFFEUR, REGGIE.
我认识袭击巴士的那些飞车党中的一个 柴瑞・甘孜
I RECOGNIZED ONE OF THOSE BIKERS THAT ATTACKED THE BUS.
他是甘孜的弟弟，和他相比 甘孜简直就是甘地
HIS NAME IS CHERRY GANZ. HE'S GANZ' BROTHER.
- 为什么冰人要用他？ - 我帮你杀了他哥哥
GANZ' BROTHER?
HE MAKES GANZ LOOK LIKE GANDHI.
WHY WOULD THE ICEMAN HIRE GANZ' BROTHER?
I RATTED GANZ TO YOU, AND YOU KILLED GANZ.
甘孜说他的弟弟 跟一个叫安琪的妓女有来往
WHO'D WANT TO KILL US MORE?
GANZ SAID HIS BROTHER FUCKED THIS BITCH NAMED ANGEL.
- 她在谷仓酒吧工作 - 我们曾收到那酒吧的投诉
HE SAID HOW INSANE THE PUSSY WAS.
SAID THE BITCH WORKED AT BARNSTORMERS.
A COUPLE BIKERS ROUSTED A BAR CALLED BARNSTORMERS.
警察们到底有没有开始调查？
THE COPS ARE ACTUALLY CONTRIBUTING TO THIS INVESTIGATION?
在监狱里待了7年怎么还记得这么多？
I'M SHOCKED.
HOW DO YOU REMEMBER WHERE THIS GIRL WORKS
在监狱里你会记得所有关于娘们的事情
AFTER SEVEN YEARS IN PRISON?
AFTER SEVEN YEARS IN PRISON,
YOU REMEMBER EVERY STORY ABOUT PUSSY, TRUST ME.
等下，我要拿点东西
WAIT. I GOT TO GET SOMETHING.
杰克，这是假的
我要把它快速的晃动
HEY, JACK...
THIS SHIT IS FAKE.
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW THE DIFFERENCE
如果有人说是假的，你就麻烦大了
WHEN YOU FLASH IT FAST.
SOMEBODY SPOOKS THAT FAKE BADGE
AND YOU GET YOUR ASS WHIPPED,
你还是为自己操操心吧，雷吉
DON'T COME CRYING TO ME.
WATCH YOUR OWN ASS, REGGIE.
我们真心相爱，那是一种…
* WE WERE TWO LOVERS *
你有幸找到的双向的爱
* ONE OF A KIND *
* WE'VE SHARED LOVE THAT FEW ARE LUCKY TO FIND... *
我要去盘问那个投诉的酒吧女
I'LL GO GET SOME INFO.
你干你警察的活儿，我去找那些妓女
A BARMAID CALLED IN THE COMPLAINT.
YOU GO DO YOUR COP SHIT, JACK.
I'M GOING TO CHECK OUT THESE WHORES.
* NOT TOO LONG AGO YOU CAME AFTER ME *
* BUT NOW IT SEEMS YOU FORGET A GUY CAN SEE *
* I'M A-BEGGING FOR LOVE *
* I CAN'T BREAK FREE *
嘿！是你投诉飞车党的吗？
* YOU'RE ALL THAT I NEED... **
YOU THE ONE WHO COMPLAINED ABOUT SOME BIKERS?
你们终于有反应了 只不过晚了一天半而已
CALL THE NEWS. COP FINALLY RESPONDED.
- 你还要继续投诉吗？ - 当我们需要你们的时候你们却不在
IT'S ONLY BEEN A DAY AND A HALF.
ARE YOU GOING TO TALK OR BITCH?
YOU'RE NEVER HERE WHEN SOMEBODY NEEDS YOU.
能给我来杯伏特加吗？你好吗？
CAN I HAVE A SHOT OF STOLI?
ON THE ROCKS?
- 嗨，请我喝一杯？ - 我刚出大牢，我穷的要命
YEAH. GREAT.
HEY. HOW YOU DOING?
BUY ME A DRINK?
- 但你可以请我喝一杯 - 滚一边儿去
I JUST GOT OUT OF JAIL.
YOU CAN BUY MY DRINK.
FUCK OFF.
我认识你，对吗？你曾经伤过我的心
HI.
I KNOW YOU, RIGHT?
YEAH, YOU DO.
- 这次我不会让你跑掉 - 我马上回来
YOU BROKE MY HEART ONCE.
DID I?
I'M NOT LETTING YOU GET AWAY THIS TIME.
我要补补妆
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
WE COULD TAKE MINE.
I HAVE TO POWDER MY NOSE.
- 嘿，你好吗？ - 不错，你好吗？
HEY!
HEY, HOW YOU DOING?
PRETTY GOOD. HOW ARE YOU?
你有没有看过那些电视广告？
ALL RIGHT.
YOU EVER SEE THOSE COMMERCIALS ON TV
- 卡尔・莫尔登 - 是的，那个大鼻子
WITH THE, UH, TOURISTS?
WITH THE GUY WITH THE BIG NOSE?
你看过他们以慢动作显示人们如何被扒？
KARL MALDEN.
THE BIG-ASS NOSE MAN.
YOU SEE THOSE COMMERCIALS WHERE HE SHOWS
PEOPLE GETTING THEIR POCKETS PICKED?
- 倒霉！ - 对于那事倒霉是个很好的形容词
YEAH.
SHIT!
- 我可以拿回你的钱 - 要多少酬劳？
SHIT IS A GOOD WORD TO SAY THERE.
I CAN GET YOUR MONEY BACK,
- 我想大概一家一半 - 平分？不要这样对我
BUT IT'S GOING TO COST YOU.
HOW MUCH?
I THINK HALF YOUR MONEY WOULD BE GOOD.
我对你够不错了，你现在可啥都没有
GIVE ME A BREAK!
I'M GIVING YOU A BREAK.
她会使用你的信用卡，你的信用要出问题了
YOU AIN'T GOT NOTHING NOW.
THE BITCH IS COUNTING YOUR MONEY.
SHE'S GOT YOUR CREDIT CARDS,
- 如果你不愿意，那就算了 - 成交
RUN YOUR RATES UP,
YOUR CREDIT'S GOING TO BE FUCKED UP.
他询问我关于在这儿工作的一个姑娘 他真的很粗鲁
YOU GOT A DEAL.
THE DARK-HAIRED GUY ASKED ABOUT A GIRL WHO WORKED HERE.
- 然后那个金毛拿出一把枪 - 那个姑娘怎么样了？
HE STARTS GRABBING ME.
THE BLOND ONE PULLS OUT A GUN.
安琪，她在北湾的鸟笼酒吧跳舞
WHAT ABOUT THIS GIRL?
ANGEL STOP WORKING HERE A YEAR AGO.
- 你为什么不把这些写下来？ - 我记性好，你知道地址？
SHE'S DANCING AT THE BIRD CAGE.
AREN'T YOU SUPPOSED TO BE WRITING THIS DOWN?
I GOT A PHOTOGRAPHIC MEMORY.
YOU GOT HER ADDRESS?
- 这是女厕 - 不关你事
THIS IS THE LADIES' ROOM.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO BE HERE.
MIND YOUR OWN BUSINESS.
嘿…
HEY.
我觉得我们应该好好认识一下 你挺麻利的
I THOUGHT THIS WOULD BE A GOOD TIME
FOR US TO GET TO KNOW EACH OTHER.
YOU'RE VERY SMOOTH. VERY, VERY SMOOTH.
我见过很多扒手，但没见过这么麻利的
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF POCKETS PICKED,
那家伙很不开心 我告诉他可以拿回一半的钱
BUT NO ONE AS SMOOTH AS YOU.
I WAS TALKING TO THE GUY YOU HIT.
HE'S UPSET.
I TOLD HIM I'D GET HALF HIS MONEY BACK.
如果你收买我 我可以告诉他你很狡猾我对付不了
THAT IS, UNLESS YOU OFFER ME A LITTLE BRIBE.
THEN I'LL TELL HIM YOU WERE TOO FAST FOR ME.
我狡猾的难以对付
I AM TOO FAST FOR YOU.
哦，嗨，差不多完事了
HI. ALMOST FINISHED.
- 还有其他人吗？ - 没了，只有这三个
WAS ANYBODY ELSE WITH THEM?
有一个瘦瘦的黑人 那个年岁大的正跟他谈话
NO. JUST THE THREE OF THEM.
THERE WAS THIS BLACK GUY.
THE OLDEST ONE WAS TALKING TO A BLACK GUY.
黑人？跟这个像吗？
A BLACK GUY, HUH?
是的，就是他，他还不错，没骚扰我
WAS IT SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
YEAH. YEAH, THAT'S HIM.
HE WAS OK.
HE DIDN'T BOTHER ME.
如果他们再来就报警，找基欧探员
IF THEY COME IN AGAIN,
CALL DOWN TO THE DEPARTMENT.
YOU ASK FOR INSPECTOR BEN KEHOE.
- 这是你的那一半钱 - 我的信用卡呢？
HE'LL KNOW WHAT TO DO.
YOU'RE LUCKY. HERE'S HALF YOUR MONEY.
这交易只是要钱，你的信用卡在厕所呢
WHAT ABOUT MY CREDIT CARDS?
WE HAD NO CREDIT CARD DEAL.
YOUR CARDS ARE STILL IN THE BATHROOM.
你必须付出你全部所得
* GOT TO GIVE IT ALL YOU GOT *
* TILL YOU DROP *
* NOW SOMETIMES YOU WIN *
- 杰克・凯茨，记得我吗？ - 我没印象了
* SOMETIMES YOU LOSE *
JACK CATES?
REMEMBER ME?
我在车后座搞一个姑娘时你拘捕了我
NAH. I DON'T THINK SO.
YOU BUSTED ME IN A CAMARO WITH A GIRL.
- 听起来不像我 - 后来才知道她未成年
THAT DON'T SOUND LIKE ME.
- 糟糕的事情发生了 - 我没有偷车，我朋友干的
TURNS OUT SHE WAS UNDERAGE,
BUT I DIDN'T KNOW IT.
SHIT HAPPENS.
- 你应该挑些好朋友 - 我被判入狱两年
MY BUDDY STOLE THE CAR.
MAYBE YOU BETTER PICK BETTER BUDDIES.
I GOT TO SEE SOMEBODY.
我不想在酒吧打架
I GOT TWO YEARS.
人们经常在酒吧打架，不老套吗？
GIVE ME A BREAK.
I DON'T WANT TO GET IN A BAR FIGHT.
PEOPLE ARE ALWAYS GETTING IN BAR FIGHTS.
你可以在电影里看到的情节
IT'S A DAMN CLICHE.
YOU ALWAYS HEAR ABOUT IT.
人们被啤酒瓶和家具敲脑袋…
YOU SEE IT IN MOVIES.
PEOPLE GET HIT IN THE HEAD
WITH BEER BOTTLES AND FURNITURE.
我要踢你两年屁股！
I'M TAKING TWO YEARS OUT OF YOUR ASS, CATES!
你有手枪吗？说不定他们有防备
YOU GOT A GUN?
IN CASE THEY STICK THE PLACE UP.
好了，不要闹了
ALL RIGHT.
我今天很倒霉，我刚刚出狱
KNOCK THIS SHIT OFF.
I'VE BEEN HAVING A VERY BAD DAY.
我被人枪击，坐的巴士翻了17个滚
I JUST GOT OUT OF JAIL THIS MORNING.
ALREADY I'VE BEEN SHOT AT,
MY BUS FLIPPED OVER 17 TIMES,
一个妓女想用刀捅我 有人炸了我的保时捷
A BITCH TRIED TO STAB ME IN THE BATHROOM,
AND SOMEBODY BLEW UP MY PORSCHE.
我通常见死不救的
I'M IN A BAD MOOD.
I USUALLY DON'T JUMP IN
但是杰克・凯茨要帮我解决一些事情
WHEN SOMEBODY'S GETTING BEAT DOWN,
BUT THIS MAN WILL HELP ME STRAIGHTEN UP MY DAY.
- 现在我们谈正经事吧 - 因为你有枪？
BACK UP AND LET US GO ABOUT OUR BUSINESS.
- 因为我会一枪打穿你的屁股 - 你没胆这样做的
BECAUSE YOU GOT A GUN?
NO. BECAUSE I HAVE A GUN AND I'LL SHOOT YOU.
I DON'T THINK YOU'VE GOT THE GUTS TO USE IT.
还有人相当瘸子吗？
ANYBODY ELSE WANT TO LIMP?
为那个膝盖道歉，我有点紧张
SORRY ABOUT THE KNEECAP.
- 你真会调查 - 你跟我玩失踪
I GOT A LITTLE EXCITED.
YOU KNOW HOW TO HANDLE AN INVESTIGATION.
- 想不到我得救你 - 我不稀罕你的帮助
YOU DISAPPEARED. WHERE WERE YOU?
I WAS IN THE BATHROOM.
THEN I GOT TO SAVE YOUR ASS.
I DIDN'T NEED YOU.
我应该带备用手枪的
I WAS PROTECTING MY MONEY.
I SHOULDN'T HAVE GONE IN THERE
然后我在酒吧打成一团 上帝啊，杰克，你在干什么？
WITHOUT MY SPARE GUN.
I GET INTO A GOD DAMN BAR FIGHT.
- 嘿！ - 这是为了什么？
JACK, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
这是为了那个篮球，现在我们扯平了 我们可以重新开始
HEY!
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
FOR THE BASKETBALL. NOW WE'RE EVEN.
我要离开这儿，交易结束了
WE CAN START FRESH.
I'VE GOT TO LEAVE, OR I'LL DO A HOMICIDE.
- 真讨厌！ - 废话，上车
THE DEAL IS OFF.
THE DEAL'S OFF, BULLSHIT.
LET'S GO. GET IN THE CAR.
你是不是从小就讨厌，或者受过训练？
COME ON.
不要这么耿耿于怀，来吧，走吧
DID YOU TAKE LESSONS TO BE A SHITHEAD?
I WAS JUST GETTING EVEN.
- 他妈的离我远点 - 别犯傻了
DON'T TAKE IT PERSONAL.
I TOLD YOU TO STAY AWAY.
I MEAN IT.
- 你要去哪儿？ - 离你远远的
HEY, DON'T BE STUPID.
WHERE YOU GOING?
AWAY! AWAY FROM YOU.
你的线索是有用的 甘孜的女友住在金美酒店
THAT'S WHERE I'M GOING.
YOUR TIP TURNED OUT OK.
GANZ' GIRL LIVES IN THE TENDERLOIN AT THE KING MEI HOTEL.
再见，杰克，去死吧，杰克
BYE, JACK.
FUCK YOU, JACK.
靠！
AW, SHIT!
这是其中一名飞车党的资料
甘孜・理查德，西部兄弟会摩托帮成员
HERE'S THE STORY ON ONE OF THE BIKERS.
GANZ, RICHARD, A.K.A. CHERRY.
身负7张拘捕令，72次违反交规
KNOWN MEMBER WESTERN BROTHERHOOD MOTORCYCLE GANG.
SEVEN OUTSTANDING WARRANTS, DETAILS TO FOLLOW.
- 洛杉矶摩托帮？ - 是的，洛杉矶警方资料更多
72 OUTSTANDING TRAFFIC VIOLATIONS.
L.A. BIKE GANGS?
LAPD TRACKED SOMETHING ON THEM A FEW MINUTES AGO.
- 我马上到 - 他是暂时停职！
MORE IS SUPPOSED TO COME IN.
ALL RIGHT. I'LL BE RIGHT OVER.
这不是一个好主意，威尔逊正在找你
THEN WHY IS HE ON THE STREETS?
COMING TO THE STATION AIN'T A GOOD IDEA.
老天啊！他知道酒吧的事了
WILSON'S LOOKING FOR YOU.
AW, CHRIST. HE HEARD ABOUT THE BAR.
带上所有资料去门口等我
15分钟
BE OUT IN FRONT IN 15 MINUTES
WITH EVERYTHING YOU GOT.
基欧，上车
KEHOE, GET IN.
- 给我，你开车 - 我的天呐！
HERE. GIVE ME THAT.
YOU TAKE THE WHEEL.
JESUS CHRIST, JACK.
- 黑考克・甘孜 - 他是阿尔伯特・甘孜的弟弟
GOT IT?
HICKOK. GANZ.
THIS GUY IS ALBERT GANZ' BROTHER.
他们是警察杀手，5天前刚枪杀了两个警察
I KNOW ALL ABOUT THAT.
THEY'RE COP KILLERS. CAPPED TWO CHIPs AND A BYSTANDER.
特别调查科说他们是帮会的执行人
A SPECIAL INVESTIGATIONS GUY IN L.A. SAID
他们跟15宗死亡案件有关，刹车，刹车！
THESE GUYS ARE ENFORCERS FOR THEIR GANG, THE BROTHERHOOD.
THEY'VE BEEN LINKED TO OVER 15 DEATHS.
- 还有其它资料吗？ - 没什么有价值的了
BRAKE! BRAKE!
YOU GOT ANYTHING ELSE?
NAH. NOTHING HARD.
- 往那边开 - 小菜一碟
JACK, JUST GO AROUND THE BLOCK.
IT'S TOO EASY.
科克兰德・史密斯，有电话找你 是雷吉・哈蒙德
KIRKLAND SMITH!
YEAH!
YOU GOT A PHONE CALL. REGGIE HAMMOND.
- 雷吉，搞定了没有？ - 有点复杂了…
REGGIE?
HEY, KIRK. WHAT'S UP?
IS IT DONE?
LOOK, IT'S A LITTLE BIT MORE COMPLICATED THAN THAT.
不要糊弄我，你不再是一个公民了
DON'T MESS WITH ME.
你不能投票，没人会雇你，你被抛弃了
YOU AIN'T A CITIZEN NO MORE.
YOU CAN'T VOTE. NOBODY WILL HIRE YOU.
你现在只剩下你的承诺了，不要对我食言
YOU'RE AN OUTCAST. NOBODY WANTS YOU.
ALL YOU GOT LEFT IS YOUR WORD.
DON'T BREAK YOUR WORD TO ME.
好地方，怎么这么久才到？
NICE PLACE, HUH?
我还以为你又退出了呢 为了啥你恋恋不舍的？
WHAT TOOK YOU SO LONG?
I THOUGHT YOU QUIT FOR THE FIFTH TIME.
我会继续下去，我们要彻底解决这事
YOU CAN'T STAY AWAY?
I'M GOING TO HANG.
WE'LL STRAIGHTEN THIS SHIT OUT.
但是，如果你再打我，如果你再抓着我…
LET ME TELL YOU SOMETHING.
IF YOU HIT ME, GRAB ME, TOUCH ME,
如果你的手再碰我…
IF YOUR HAND BRUSHES AGAINST ME LIGHTLY,
- 我会杀了你 - 我会好好对你的
I'LL KILL YOU. I'M SERIOUS.
这次我放过你，因为你很疼，哪只手来着？
DON'T WORRY. I'LL TREAT YOU RIGHT.
I LET THINGS PASS BECAUSE YOU GOT SHOT,
左手，医生说伤口深至骨头
AND YOU'RE IN A LOT OF PAIN.
WHICH ARM IS IT?
LEFT. DOC SAYS IT'S BRUISED TO THE BONE.
- 现在我们打成平手了！ - 只是篮球的事摆平了
THAT'S A DEEP BRUISE.
NOW WE EVEN, MOTHERFUCKER.
I JUST GOT EVEN FOR THE BASKETBALL, YOU SON OF A BITCH!
先把钱还我，然后你可以用球打我
RETURN MY MONEY, THEN YOU CAN HIT ME WITH THE BALL.
等下，我们去找这女的谈谈
WAIT A MINUTE, REG.
WE'RE GOING TO JUST GO AND TALK TO THIS GIRL.
- 别耍我，杰克 - 我们就是去找她谈谈而已
DON'T SNEAK ME, JACK.
IF SHE'S HERE, WE'RE GOING TO TALK TO HER.
这是警察的一般性工作
THIS IS JUST STRAIGHT-AHEAD COP STUFF, ISN'T IT?
谢谢你
HERE...OH...
WELL, THANK YOU.
给了我那个！
GIVE ME THAT.
那么柴瑞什么时候能来？
SO WHEN'S CHERRY COMING OVER?
别担心，他会来的
DON'T WORRY.
HE'LL BE BY.
他说你真的很棒，他说的没错
HE SAID YOU WERE REAL NICE.
HE WAS RIGHT.
- 我们不认识她 - 现在认识她了吗？
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
WE NEVER HEAR OF HER.
- 假警徽，我孩子也有一个 - 你孩子有这个吗？
HEARD OF HER NOW?
THAT FAKE BADGE.
MY KID GET ONE OF THOSE.
YOUR KID GOT ONE OF THESE?
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
安琪・李在楼上，四楼4B室
ANGEL LEE. UPSTAIRS.
FOURTH FLOOR. 4-B.
OK.
她可能都没见过他
CHANCES ARE SHE HASN'T EVEN SEEN THIS GUY.
他是来这儿杀人，不是找旧女友的
HE'S IN TOWN FOR A HIT.
- 会的，他会的 - 你在这儿等着，我上去看看她
HE'S NOT GOING TO POP HIS OLD GIRLFRIEND.
HE WILL, THEN SHARE WITH HIS FRIENDS.
我才不在下面等 要是那些飞车党出现了咋办？
THEY'RE LIKE ESKIMOS.
YOU WAIT HERE. I'LL SEE THE LADY.
I AIN'T WAITING HERE.
你有枪，你留下，我上去
I AIN'T GOT NO GUN.
WHAT IF THOSE BIKERS SHOW UP?
- 你要这警徽吗？ - 我不会在上面碰到小孩子的
YOU STAY HERE.
IF SHE'S THERE, I'LL SHOUT DOWN.
YOU WANT THIS BADGE?
NO. I DON'T THINK I'LL RUN INTO ANY KIDS.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
- 谁啊？ - 送披萨给安琪小姐
YEAH? WHO IS IT?
I HAVE A PIZZA DELIVERY FOR MISS ANGEL.
- 我没有订什么披萨 - 4B室，安琪小姐，披萨
I DIDN'T ORDER ANY PIZZA.
IT SAYS, UM, ROOM 4-B, MISS ANGEL,
PIZZA DELIVERY.
等等，我得穿点衣服
HANG ON A SECOND.
I GOT TO GET SOMETHING ON.
她没穿衣服！
IS SHE NAKED?
我没有订什么披萨
I DIDN'T ORDER ANY PIZZA.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
不可能的！
你他妈找死！我要杀了你
NO FUCKING WAY!
FUCKING PIG! I KILLED YOU.
你不能还活着的，我已经杀了你
YOU CAN'T BE ALIVE.
I ALREADY KILLED YOU.
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
马上打电话求救！
CALL FOR HELP NOW!
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
出了什么事？你要去哪儿？
WHAT'S GOING ON, HICKOK? WHERE YOU GOING?
[SPEAKING CHINESE]
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
你杀了我的家人，蠢猪，我要杀了你
YOU KILLED MY FAMILY, PIG!
I'M GOING TO KILL YOU.
离开这儿
他妈的猪！杂种猪！
FUCKING PIG!
MOTHERFUCKING PIG!
- 柴瑞，过来 - 你他妈要死了！
CHERRY, GET GOING! LET'S GO!
FUCKING SON OF A BITCH!
YOU'RE A FUCKING SON OF A BITCH!
YAAH!
来吧
COME ON.
COME ON!
他们在后面！
THEY'RE OUT BACK. COME ON!
[HORN HONKS]
[SHOUTING IN CHINESE]
在后面胡同里
DOWN THE ALLEY.
AAH!
YEAH!
[SIREN]
现场已经封锁，我还是没有拿到杰克的陈述
YEAH, WE GOT THE PERIMETER SECURED.
JACK'S OK.
我不知道他哪儿来的枪
I HAVEN'T GOTTEN A STATEMENT FROM HIM, THOUGH.
听着，我要一份他的陈述，好吗？
I DON'T KNOW WHOSE GUN HE USED.
LOOK, I'LL GET THE STATEMENT, OK? FINE.
- 你麻烦大了 - 告诉点我不知道的
YOU'RE IN DEEP SHIT, YOU KNOW THAT, JACK?
- 电脑系统找不到这人 - 我明白了
TELL ME SOMETHING I DON'T KNOW.
I COULDN'T COME UP WITH A MATCH ON THIS GUY.
THAT FIGURES.
好了，你将被指控为谋杀案从犯
OK. RIGHT NOW YOU'RE LOOKING AT ACCESSORY TO MURDER ONE.
即使行为良好也得蹲十年大牢
THAT GETS YOU 5 TO 10 YEARS INSIDE,
跟我们合作你可能会得到自由
AND THAT'S WITH GOOD BEHAVIOR, UNLESS YOU COOPERATE,
AND THEN YOU MIGHT NOT DO ANY TIME AT ALL.
我说过了我要见律师
I GOT NOTHING TO SAY UNTIL I TALK TO A LAWYER.
你爱柴瑞这家伙吗？我当然可以理解
ARE YOU PROTECTING CHERRY BECAUSE YOU'RE IN LOVE?
他一年来两次，让他的朋友跟你相好
I CAN CERTAINLY UNDERSTAND THAT.
WHAT DOES HE DO, BLOW THROUGH TOWN TWICE A YEAR,
喝醉后就打你，我能理解你为什么爱他
LET HIS FRIENDS JUMP UP AND DOWN ON YOU?
I CAN UNDERSTAND WHY A GIRL WOULD LOVE A GUY LIKE THAT.
他们四处漂泊，我联系不上他们
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW WHERE THEY'RE AT.
- 有谁可以？ - 我不知道，他们都是疯子
I CAN NEVER GET IN TOUCH WITH THEM.
WHO CAN?
I DON'T KNOW. THOSE GUYS ARE NUTS.
这是杰克・凯茨警官
DON'T WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING.
李小姐打算告诉我们柴瑞先生的联系人
THIS IS OFFICER JACK CATES.
MR. CATES, MISS LEE WAS ABOUT TO HELP US.
I THINK SHE WAS ABOUT TO TELL ME
THE NAME OF MR. CHERRY'S CONTACT MAN.
这人名叫马尔科姆・普莱斯 他有大的吓人的眼睛，长头发
THE GUY'S NAME IS MALCOLM PRICE.
HE HAS BIG, SPOOKY EYES. LONG HAIR.
没有人能联系上柴瑞除非先找他
NOBODY TALKS TO CHERRY UNLESS THEY TALK TO HIM FIRST.
- 在哪儿我们能找到这人？ - 我不知道
OK. NOW WHERE DO WE FIND THIS GUY?
- 嘿… - 我发誓，我只知道名字
I DON'T KNOW.
HEY.
I SWEAR. I ONLY KNOW THE NAME.
- 谢谢，宝贝 - 嘿，等一下
THANKS, BABE.
HEY, WAIT A MINUTE!
- 你要去哪儿？ - 让基欧去查马尔科姆・普莱斯
WHERE THE HELL DO YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING?
RADIO BACK TO KEHOE.
TELL HIM TO RUN A SHIT SHEET ON A BIKER--MALCOLM PRICE.
- 他应该有记录的，我们走吧 - 你麻烦大了
GOOD BET HE'S GOT A LONG RECORD.
I GOT TO GET A STATEMENT.
YOUR ASS IS GOING TO BE GRASS!
你是要去送死
AT THE RATE WE'RE GOING, YOU'LL PICK UP PRICE AT MY FUNERAL.
如果冰人抓到了你 我们连你的尸体也不会找到
DON'T WORRY ABOUT YOUR FUNERAL.
IF THE ICEMAN GETS YOU, WE WON'T FIND YOUR BODY.
我们需要一个知道来龙去脉的人
WE NEED TO TALK TO SOMEBODY WHO KNOWS ABOUT THIS.
- 我们应该回到监狱去 - 狗屁
OK, WHERE?
WE SHOULD GO BACK TO PRISON.
你想了解普莱斯，我认识一个人了解他
OH, BULLSHIT!
GOT ANY BETTER IDEAS HOW TO FIND OUT SOMETHING?
I GOT A GUY WHO KNOWS EVERYTHING ABOUT EVERYBODY.
你无论如何都应该回监狱去 因为过不久你就会享受监狱时光了
IT WOULDN'T BE BAD FOR YOU TO GO TO PRISON.
跟一些被你剥夺了权利的人重修旧好
YOU MIGHT BE SPENDING TIME THERE.
GET REACQUAINTED WITH THE BROTHERS
我只抓坏人的
WHOSE RIGHTS YOU VIOLATED.
I JUST ARREST CROOKS, I DON'T MAKE THEM STEAL.
你的意思是说他们只配当坏人
YOU MAKE IT SOUND LIKE
EVERYBODY WENT TO A GUIDANCE COUNSELOR,
AND CROOK WAS THE ONLY JOB THEY WAS QUALIFIED FOR.
这故事不错，抱怨社会吧
THAT'S A GOOD STORY, REGGIE.
BLAME IT ON SOCIETY.
如果大便也值钱，穷人便会天生没屁眼
PUT IT ON SOCIETY'S SHOULDERS.
IF SHIT WAS WORTH SOMETHING,
POOR PEOPLE WOULD BE BORN WITH NO ASSHOLES.
[RING]
是我，我听到了消息
YEAH, IT'S ME.
我警告过你要小心那些疯狂的枪手的
I HEARD ABOUT IT.
WELL, HEY, MAN, I WARNED YOU
ABOUT DEALING WITH THESE CRAZY-ASS CRACKERS.
不，我不用，那不是我的风格
WHAT? NO, I AIN'T CARRYING.
THAT AIN'T MY THING. YOU KNOW THAT.
我也是一个生意人，但我不想离他们太近
LOOK, I'M A BUSINESSMAN, TOO,
BUT I DON'T WANT TO GET TOO CLOSE TO THESE GUYS.
这些人剥夺了我工作的全部乐趣
THESE GUYS ARE TAKING THE FUN OUT OF MY WORK.
我记得
RIGHT.
YEAH, I REMEMBER. I REMEMBER.
你不用提醒我
I SAID YOU DON'T HAVE TO REMIND ME OF IT, OK?
别担心，我会安排妥当
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
I'LL PULL IT TOGETHER.
科克兰德，有人找你
GOOD MORNING, KIRKLAND. YOU GOT SOME VISITORS.
HEY, MAN, WOULD YOU SHUT UP OVER THERE?
把那人的照片拿来
GET THAT PICTURE OF THE GUY.
一个叫伯勒斯的小贩子，被冰人雇用
HE'S A SMALL-TIME DEALER. HIS NAME IS...BURROUGHS.
RECRUITED BY THE ICEMAN A COUPLE OF MONTHS AGO.
你认识他老板马尔科姆・普莱斯？
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT THE GUY HE WORKS FOR NAMED MALCOLM PRICE?
我认识他，西部兄弟会
YEAH, I KNOW HIM. WESTERN BROTHERHOOD.
如果你要找他们杀人，你得先找普莱斯
WANT THESE GUYS TO DO A HIT FOR YOU,
- 你有地址码？ - 我不知道，你自己去找吧
YOU GOT TO GO THROUGH PRICE.
YOU GOT AN ADDRESS?
在环城路的日落汽车旅馆，把电话给雷吉
I'M NOT 411. YOU LOOK IT UP.
SUNSET MOTEL ON THE BELTWAY.
GIVE THE PHONE BACK TO REGGIE.
他有什么问题？你能走开吗？ 我有话要和这儿的兄弟说
WHAT'S HIS PROBLEM?
I DON'T KNOW.
DO YOU MIND? I'M TRYING TO TALK TO THE BROTHER HERE.
能否请你走开？我兄弟要跟我谈黑人的事
I'LL HANDLE THIS. CAN YOU EXCUSE ME?
ME AND MY BROTHER WANT TO TALK.
- 是私事 - 请吧
IT'S BLACK STUFF. EXCUSE US.
IT'S PRIVATE.
YOU MIND? YOU MIND?
你可否去那边？谢谢
HANG ON.
CAN YOU GO OVER THERE?
- 是私事 - 好吧
THANK YOU.
IT'S PRIVATE.
听着，我已经给了你要的东西…第二次了
ALL RIGHT, ALL RIGHT.
REGGIE, LOOK. NOW THAT I'VE GIVEN YOU SOMETHING YOU NEED...
对，我感激你的忍耐，谢谢
FOR THE SECOND TIME...
YES, YOU HAVE, AND I APPRECIATE YOUR PATIENCE,
你要…还欠我的债！
AND THANK YOU.
YOU WILL... REPAY YOUR DEBT TO ME!
嘿，哥们，不用担心，我们留了很多后手
HEY, MAN, NOT TO WORRY.
WE GOT LOTS OF BACKUP.
过来喝杯酒
COME ON IN AND HAVE A DRINK.
[GUNSHOTS]
马尔科姆・普莱斯
MALCOLM PRICE.
这肯定是一个好线索，有人向他开了16枪
MUST HAVE BEEN A REAL GOOD LEAD, JACK.
多年来我一直在查冰人，总是走上死胡同
SOMEBODY SHOT HIM 16 TIMES.
I'VE BEEN CHASING THIS GOD DAMN ICEMAN FOR YEARS.
EVERY TIME I GET CLOSE,
- 这工作会让你发疯 - 是啊，是啊…
IT'S ANOTHER GOD DAMN DEAD END.
THIS JOB WILL DRIVE YOU CRAZY.
YEAH, YEAH, YEAH.
- 杰克，冰人是一个警察 - 不可能
JACK, THE ICEMAN'S A COP.
把事情联系起来
NO WAY.
COME ON, JACK. PUT THE SHIT TOGETHER, MAN.
你查普莱斯的地址，冰人快你一步
JACK, THINK ABOUT IT.
YOU CALLED FOR PRICE'S ADDRESS.
- 这是巧合，运气不好 - 不是巧合
THE ICEMAN SHOWS UP THERE FIRST.
IT'S A COINCIDENCE. BAD LUCK.
还有那张图片？
WHAT ABOUT THE BROTHER WHOSE PICTURE YOU'VE BEEN SHOWING AROUND?
你用电脑系统查面部图片
GET ANY FEEDBACK ON THAT?
YOU GOT TO RUN A MUG SHOT THROUGH NCIC.
- 需要多长时间？ - 数小时…有时更慢
HOW LONG THAT TAKE?
HOURS.
知道冰人为什么要杀我？跟钱没有关系
IT'S BEEN HOURS.
WELL, SOMETIMES IT'S SLOW.
THE ICEMAN WANTS TO KILL ME.
IT HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE MONEY I TOOK.
他要杀我是因为我见过他，我可以揭穿他
HE WANT TO KILL ME BECAUSE I SEEN HIM.
查出谁最努力阻止你查这案子
HE THINKS I CAN BLOW HIS COVER.
THE SAME GUY IS FUCKING UP YOUR INVESTIGATION.
WHO'S PUTTING UP RESISTANCE 'CAUSE YOU'RE ON THIS CASE?
他就很可能是冰人
THAT IS PROBABLY THE ICEMAN.
肯定是威尔逊，那家伙多年来一直针对我
ONLY GUY IT COULD BE IS WILSON,
AND THAT PRICK'S BEEN DOGGING MY ASS FOR YEARS,
从我刚开始查冰人起他便这样
EVER SINCE I STARTED LOOKING FOR THE ICEMAN.
我必须和你到聆讯法庭去辨认这个人
ALL THROUGH THIS THING!
I GOT TO GET YOU TO THE HEARING.
他们可能已经决心把我踢出警察队伍 聆讯两小时前已经开始了
WHAT HEARING?
THE ONE WHERE THEY'RE GOING TO TAKE AWAY MY BADGE.
事后，凯茨探员
IT STARTED TWO HOURS AGO.
他极力坚持有一名罪犯在背后操纵海湾区
AFTER THE INCIDENT IN THE MISSION DISTRICT,
INSPECTOR CATES DREDGED UP THIS THEORY
四年来他浪费资源和人力
OF A CRIMINAL MASTERMIND RUNNING THE DRUG TRAFFIC
IN THE BAY AREA.
FOR FOUR YEARS,
试图证明他自己和他的理论
HE HAS WASTED DEPARTMENT RESOURCES AND MANPOWER,
描述他的职业操守
RISKED OTHER OFFICERS' LIVES TO VINDICATE HIS THEORIES.
CAN YOU DESCRIBE INSPECTOR CATES' PROFESSIONAL ATTITUDE?
当一名警官为了自己而凌驾部门的纪律之上
WHEN A POLICE OFFICER TAKES IT UPON HIMSELF
TO VIOLATE DEPARTMENT REGULATIONS
这就会使好警察也做不好工作
AND SUSPECTS' CIVIL RIGHTS,
IT MAKES IT HARD ON EVERY GOOD COP
反对，这些评论与案件无关
OUT THERE TRYING TO DO HIS JOB.
THESE REMARKS HAVE NOTHING TO DO WITH THE INCIDENT.
我要证明一种行为方式
ON THE CONTRARY, YOUR HONOR.
它将有助于了解亨特角赛车场所发生的事
I'M TRYING TO SHOW A PATTERN OF BEHAVIOR
证词有效
THAT WILL ILLUMINATE EVENTS AT HUNTER'S POINT RACEWAY.
I'LL LET THE TESTIMONY STAND.
根据州政府提供的初步证据
IN CONSIDERATION OF THE PRELIMINARY EVIDENCE
以及遵循加利福尼亚州法律…
PRESENTED THUS FAR BY THE STATE,
AND IN ADHERENCE TO LAWS, STATUTES, AND RULES
SPECIFIED BY THE STATE OF CALIFORNIA,
- 就是他！ - 肃静！这是在聆讯
CITY OF SAN FRANCISCO--
THERE HE IS!
ORDER! ORDER! LET'S HAVE SOME ORDER HERE.
- 不，另有其人 - 不，就在那儿
THIS IS AN OFFICIAL HEARING.
NO, IT'S SOME OTHER GUY.
不是他
NO, NO, NO! RIGHT THERE.
- 这些人是谁？ - 法官大人，那就是凯茨探员
THAT'S NOT HIM.
THAT'S HIM.
WHO ARE THESE MEN?
- 肯定不是他 - 他肯定就是冰人
THAT IS INSPECTOR JACK CATES.
THAT'S DEFINITELY NOT THE GUY.
他不是那个被我取了钱的人
THAT'S GOT TO BE THE ICEMAN.
- 他肯定就是冰人 - 太过分了！
YOU DON'T FORGET SOMEBODY YOU TOOK HALF A MILLION FROM.
THAT'S GOT TO BE THE ICEMAN!
THIS IS TOO MUCH!
本州将会对凯茨探员进行刑事审判
THIS COURT RULES THAT THERE IS SUFFICIENT EVIDENCE
TO PROCEED WITH A CRIMINAL TRIAL
审判将尽早进行
AGAINST INSPECTOR JACK CATES.
TRIAL DATE WILL BE SET
FOR THE EARLIEST OPENING ON THE COURT CALENDAR.
THIS HEARING IS ADJOURNED.
- 冰人干掉了普莱斯 - 你想说什么？
ICEMAN WHACKED OUT PRICE.
他没有选择，你的女友向警察出卖了他
YOU WANT TO TALK ABOUT IT?
NO CHOICE. YOUR GIRL RATTED HIM OUT TO THE COPS.
这不是瞎说，你们都认识她 她住在金美酒店
BULLSHIT.
I DON'T BULLSHIT.
SHE WORKS AS A DANCER,
你们应该小心与你们所来往的人
LIVES AT THE KING MEI HOTEL.
YOU SHOULD BE MORE CAREFUL ABOUT WHO YOU HANG OUT WITH.
- 谁开的枪？ - 有什么不同吗？
WHO PULLED THE TRIGGER?
WHAT'S THE FUCKING DIFFERENCE WHO PULLED THE TRIGGER?
警察险些得手，做事而已，不针对任何人
THE COPS WERE GETTING TOO CLOSE.
THAT'S THE WAY THE MAN DOES BUSINESS.
你应该明白不同之处
BUSINESS, NOT PERSONAL.
做事…对
YOU TWO FUCKING HILLBILLIES
SHOULD LEARN THE DIFFERENCE.
BUSINESS. YEAH.
AAH!
这也是做事而已
THAT'S BUSINESS, TOO.
你现在高兴了，混蛋？
YOU HAPPY NOW, ASSHOLE?
这样仍不会改变你要做的事
THAT STILL DOESN'T CHANGE THE JOB.
- 你必须得干掉哈蒙德 - 我们怎么干？
YOU GOT TO KILL REGGIE HAMMOND.
是科克兰德・史密斯保护雷吉在狱中生存
HOW WILL WE DO THAT?
KIRKLAND SMITH KEPT REGGIE ALIVE
WHEN WE HAD PAPERS OUT ON HIM.
雷吉欠他的人情，他要偿还
REGGIE OWES HIM. I FIGURED OUT WHERE HE'LL PAY BACK.
这哥们有个女儿在海特・古德威尔商场工作
THE DUDE'S GOT A DAUGHTER
WORKS IN A GOODWILL STORE
我们要干掉哈蒙德和那个警察以及冰人
IN THE HAIGHT JUST OFF CENTRAL.
WE'RE GOING TO GET HAMMOND,
THEN WE'RE GOING TO GET THE COP AND THE ICEMAN,
- 我们要把他们都干掉 - 先集中对付哈蒙德，乡巴佬
AND WE'RE GOING TO KILL THEM ALL.
YOU JUST STICK TO HAMMOND, JOE BOB. THAT'S THE GIG.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
我总是忘掉开锁密码
I KEEP FORGETTING THE COMBINATION.
我不想看你开锁，我们可以抓到他的
I DON'T WANT TO SEE YOU CLEAR OUT YOUR LOCKER.
WE CAN GET THIS GUY.
我当了20年警察
YOU KNOW, REGGIE, I'VE BEEN A COP FOR 20 YEARS,
整天面对皮条客，杀人犯和劫匪
AND ALL I'VE BEEN AROUND IS PIMPS, MURDERERS, AND ROBBERS,
我对你一向坦率，你尽了力…
BUT BETWEEN YOU AND ME, I'VE ALWAYS BEEN STRAIGHT.
NOW, YOU DID YOUR BEST.
这是你的四十七万五千块
SO HERE'S YOUR 475 THOU.
你把我的钱放在你的储物柜？警察储物柜，杰克？
YOU KEPT MY MONEY IN YOUR LOCKER?
耶！嘿，我们没关系了，你自由了，雷吉
YEAH.
IN A POLICE LOCKER?
YEAH. HEY, WE GOT NO MORE TIES.
我给你的忠告是，把钱拿走然后消失
YOU'RE A FREE MAN, REG.
LISTEN, MY ADVICE TO YOU IS TAKE THIS MONEY AND DISAPPEAR.
- 你确定吗，哥们？ - 是的
YOU SURE, MAN?
YEP.
好吧
ALL RIGHT.
谢谢，祝你今天愉快
THANK YOU. HAVE A NICE DAY.
雷吉・哈蒙德，这是七万五 你父亲的意思
HAMMOND. REGGIE HAMMOND.
THIS IS $75,000, COURTESY OF YOUR FATHER.
- 这钱一定没好来路 - 我们都知道你父亲不是天使
FROM KIRKLAND SMITH? IT'S GOT TO BE DIRTY.
这钱不是偷的 当我在牢里的时候他帮助了我
YOUR FATHER'S NO ANGEL,
BUT THIS MONEY IS NOT STOLEN.
YOUR FATHER DID A FAVOR FOR ME.
我欠他的人情，他觉得这会对你有用
I OWED MONEY TO YOUR FATHER.
许多父亲是不会这样干的，拿着吧，再见
HE THOUGHT IT WOULD BENEFIT YOU.
I THINK YOU SHOULD ACCEPT IT.
哈蒙德先生，他好吗？
BYE-BYE.
MR. HAMMOND.
他很好，你应该去看看他
HOW IS HE?
HE'S GOOD. YOU SHOULD GO SEE HIM.
- 也许吧 - 不，你应该去看看他
MAYBE.
NO, NO MAYBE. YOU SHOULD GO SEE HIM.
SHH. SHH.
- 嘿 - 嗨，本
HEY.
- 抱歉，我不能帮太多的忙 - 你已经尽力了
HI, BEN.
SORRY I COULDN'T HELP MORE, JACK.
IT'S ALL RIGHT. YOU DID WHAT YOU COULD.
没有你这里肯定很枯燥
IT'LL BE PRETTY FUCKING DULL
WITHOUT YOU AROUND HERE.
我不敢相信你明天就不来了
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU'RE NOT COMING TO WORK TOMORROW.
- 来瓶啤酒？ - 等等再说
GET A BEER?
MAYBE LATER.
- 有许多给你的留言，弗兰克 - 谢谢，乔
YOU GOT A BUNCH OF MESSAGES, FRANK.
THANKS, JOE.
- 喂？ - 我们抓到了哈蒙德
- 好，他死了吗？ - 计划有点变动
YEAH.
WE GOT HAMMOND.
GOOD.
- 杀了我们一个人不是交易内容 - 这是什么话？
IS HE DEAD YET?
THERE'S A CHANGE. KILLING ONE OF US WASN'T PART OF THE DEAL.
你想让他死，就给我们五十万
WHAT KIND OF SHIT ARE YOU PULLING?
为了我们的一个兄弟
500 Gs. THAT'S THE PRICE FOR YOU DOING ONE OF THE BROTHERHOOD.
五十万或是哈蒙德指证你 在莫德斯托有个地方…
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
500,000, OR WE LET HAMMOND FINGER YOU.
你要更多的钱，就找个室内场所，人多点的
THERE'S A PLACE OUT OF MODESTO--
ARE YOU NUTS? NO WAY.
YOU WANT MORE MONEY, PICK A NEW PLACE.
SOMETHING INDOORS, SOMETHING WITH LOTS OF PEOPLE.
有个叫伯勒斯的家伙好像就是你在找的那人
JACK, THIS JUST CAME IN.
SOME GUY NAMED BURROUGHS LOOKS LIKE THE GUY YOU WERE AFTER.
他们在米申找到了他的尸体
这是他的资料，长的不得了
THEY FOUND HIM DEAD IN THE MISSION A WHILE AGO.
HERE'S HIS SHEET. IT'S A MILE LONG.
我曾在这儿传阅这人的照片，一无所获
I CIRCULATED THIS GUY'S PICTURE AT THE PRECINCT LAST NIGHT.
真好笑，克鲁斯去年七月逮捕了他
I GOT NOTHING.
THAT'S FUNNY. CRUISE BUSTED HIM LAST JULY.
凯茨，虽然我们之间没有感情
CATES, EVEN THOUGH THERE'S NO LOVE LOST BETWEEN US,
但我也不希望看到一个男人抛弃了他的事业 过去的就让它过去吧
IT HURTS TO SEE A MAN THROW AWAY HIS CAREER.
LET'S LET BYGONES BE BY--
我在找鸟笼俱乐部的高级部分
HEY, I'M LOOKING FOR THE CAGE CLUB.
五楼，你要加入，收五十块
THE UPSTAIRS PART.
FIFTH FLOOR.
YOU GOT TO JOIN. 50 BUCKS.
你看起来不太高兴，雷吉
YOU DON'T LOOK TOO HAPPY, REG.
对不起，等会儿我请你喝酒
SORRY, BABE. I'LL BUY YOU A DRINK LATER.
哈蒙德呢？
WHERE'S HAMMOND?
- 那女的是谁？ - 只是碰巧和他在一起的
WHO'S THE GIRL?
JUST SOMEBODY HE WAS WITH.
是五十万吧？现在我们开始验货
500 Gs, RIGHT?
NOW, LET'S CHECK THE MERCHANDISE.
从后门带出去弄死，两个都弄死
TAKE HIM OUT BEHIND THE BUILDING AND BLOW HIM AWAY.
这人来这儿干什么？那人不是冰人
SHOOT THE GIRL, TOO.
WHAT'S THIS GUY DOING HERE?
THAT GUY AIN'T THE ICEMAN.
- 你只想救自己 - 那家伙是个警察，这是陷阱
YOU'RE JUST TRYING TO SAVE YOUR ASS, REG.
THAT GUY IS A COP. YOU'RE GETTING SET UP.
他们找错人了，是不是，克鲁斯？
THEY GOT THE WRONG GUY, DON'T THEY, CRUISE?
你好，杰克
HELLO, JACK.
现在是圣诞节，威利 我们可以把他们一网打尽
IT'S CHRISTMAS HERE, WILLIE.
那就是冰人！
WE CAN TAKE THEM ALL-- HAMMOND, THE PIG, THE ICEMAN.
太好了，杰克，你永远是一个聪明的警察
THAT'S HIM! THAT'S THE ICEMAN RIGHT THERE.
PRETTY GOOD, JACK. YOU ALWAYS WERE A SMART COP.
- 我真不敢相信 - 让你失望真不好意思，杰克
BEN, I REALLY DIDN'T WANT TO BELIEVE IT.
我只想抓住冰人，你们两个，拿钱走人
SORRY TO LET YOU DOWN, JACK.
ALL I WANT'S THE ICEMAN.
- 没人能拿走我的钱 - 钱？我只要他妈的冰人
YOU TWO TAKE THE MONEY.
AIN'T NOBODY LEAVING WITH MY MONEY.
MONEY? I WANT THE FUCKING ICEMAN.
YAAH!
AAH!
他妈的给我滚
GET THE FUCK OUT OF THE WAY!
YAAH!
EAT SHIT!
GET THE FUCK OUT OF HERE!
GET OUT!
操！
[CLICK CLICK]
FUCK!
GET THE FUCK OUT OF MY WAY!
- 救命啊！ - 闭嘴！
PLEASE HELP ME!
SOMEBODY HELP ME! AAH!
SHUT UP!
放了我
FUCK! FUCK YOU! LET GO OF ME!
你这贱货！
LET GO! NO!
OH, YOU FUCKING BITCH!
YOU FUCKING BIT ME, YOU FUCKING BITCH!
你陷害我，本，你根本没用电脑系统查资料
YOU SET ME UP, BEN!
你让克鲁斯在赛车场拿走了枪
YOU NEVER RAN THAT SHIT THROUGH NCIC.
我得阻挠你，你几乎查出真相
YOU HAD CRUISE PICK UP THE GUN AT THE TRACK.
I NEEDED LEVERAGE. YOU WERE GETTING CLOSE.
YAAH!
[CLICK]
FUCK YOU!
YAAH!
杰克，我们可以商量商量，放我走吧
WE CAN WORK THIS OUT. JUST LET ME OUT OF HERE.
你是一个耻辱，本 没什么比坏警察更糟的了
YOU'RE A DISGRACE, BEN.
NOTHING WORSE THAN A BAD COP.
谢谢你给我一个如此美好的一天！
HEY, JACK, THANK YOU FOR A VERY PLEASANT DAY.
我没有车，没有钱
I GOT NO CAR, I GOT NO MONEY,
现在还被毒贩用微冲指着太阳穴
AND I'LL END THE DAY WITH THIS DOPEMAN'S UZI BY MY TEMPLE.
今天是杰克日，为何不让杰克开枪打我？ 开枪吧，杰克！
LOOK, THIS IS JACK'S DAY.
LET JACK SHOOT ME.
JACK, WHY DON'T YOU SHOOT ME?
我要过去
COMING THROUGH.
哦，杰克，我不敢相信你开枪打我 真是伤心啊
OH, JACK. I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU SHOT ME, MAN.
我跟你说过要买件防弹衣的
THIS SHIT HURTS.
YOU SHOULD HAVE BOUGHT A DAMN BULLETPROOF VEST.
你干的真好，雷吉
YOU DID GOOD, REGGIE.
大夫说你会好起来的 我猜我的枪法真的不错
YOU DID REAL GOOD.
THE DOC SAYS YOU'S GOING TO BE FINE.
GUESS I'M A PRETTY GOOD SHOT, HUH?
- 你必须不能紧张 - 我很遗憾他是你朋友
YOU'RE GOING TO HAVE TO TAKE IT EASY.
他不是我朋友，你才是
I'M SORRY YOU HAD TO KNOCK YOUR FRIEND.
HE WASN'T MY FRIEND. YOU'RE MY FRIEND.
而且，我必须救我的拍档
BESIDES, I HAD TO SAVE MY PARTNER, DIDN'T I?
我从冰人那里弄的
I GOT THIS OFF THE ICEMAN.
这是五十万，我会去医院看你 然后咱谈谈它
IT'S 500 GRAND.
I'LL MEET YOU AT THE HOSPITAL.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT, OK?
给，帮我拿着
HERE. HOLD THIS FOR ME.
[SIREN]
* WELL, THERE'S A REASON *
* EVERYBODY SHOULD BE SHAKIN' IN THE HOUSE TONIGHT *
* AND YOU SHOULD GRAB YOUR FAVORITE LADY *
* AND PROMISE HER YOU'LL DO IT RIGHT *
* TELL BAD JACK TO JUMP BACK *
* AND GIVE YOU A SHOT OF SOME BOOZE *
* SO YOU CAN PARTY TO SOME STOMP-DOWN *
* BUTT-BUMPIN' ROCK 'N' ROLL RHYTHM-AND-BLUES *
* 'CAUSE THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* I KNOW THAT EVERYBODY, WHEN THEY HEAR THE MUSIC *
* THEY'LL BE DOIN' IT ON THE FLOOR *
* JUMP UP AND DOWN AND TURN AROUND *
* AND TELL THE BAND TO PLAY SOME MORE *
* SO TONIGHT YOU CAN DANCE AND ROMANCE *
* AND DO ANYTHING YOU FEEL LIKE DOIN' *
* SO DON'T LOOK SURPRISED *
* 'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT I LIKE *
* AND TONIGHT WE OUGHT TO DO IT *
* 'CAUSE THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* OH, YEAH *
* WELL, THERE'S A REASON *
* EVERYBODY SHOULD BE SHAKIN' IN THE HOUSE TONIGHT *
* AND YOU SHOULD GRAB YOUR FAVORITE LADY *
* AND PROMISE HER YOU'LL DO IT RIGHT *
* TELL BAD JACK TO JUMP BACK *
* AND GIVE YOU A SHOT OF SOME BOOZE *
* SO YOU CAN PARTY TO SOME STOMP-DOWN *
* BUTT-BUMPIN' ROCK 'N' ROLL RHYTHM-AND-BLUES *
* 'CAUSE THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* YEAH, YEAH, YEAH *
* AND WHEN THE BOYS ARE BACK *
* THERE AIN'T NO FOOLIN' AROUND *
* WHOO *
* 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3 *
* WELL, THERE'S A REASON *
* EVERYBODY SHOULD BE SHAKIN' IN THE HOUSE TONIGHT *
* AND YOU SHOULD GRAB YOUR FAVORITE LADY *
* AND PROMISE HER TO DO IT RIGHT *
* TELL BAD JACK TO JUMP BACK *
* AND GIVE YOU A SHOT OF SOME BOOZE *
* SO YOU CAN PARTY TO SOME STOMP-DOWN *
* BUTT-BUMPIN' ROCK 'N' ROLL RHYTHM-AND-BLUES *
* YES, YOU KNOW *
* THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* OH, YEAH *
* I KNOW THAT EVERYBODY, WHEN THEY HEAR THE MUSIC *
* WILL BE DOIN' IT ON THE FLOOR *
* JUMP UP AND DOWN AND TURN AROUND *
* AND TELL THE BAND TO PLAY SOME MORE *
* SO TONIGHT YOU CAN DANCE AND ROMANCE *
* AND DO ANYTHING YOU FEEL LIKE DOIN' *
* SO DON'T LOOK SURPRISED *
* 'CAUSE YOU KNOW WHAT I LIKE *
* AND TONIGHT WE OUGHT TO DO IT *
* OH, YEAH *
* THE BOYS ARE BACK IN TOWN *
* IN TOWN OH, YEAH, WOW... **